<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string name="BeginningBVS">
        I arrive at school, the place I dread the most. Why you ask?
        Well, considering that I get “bullied” there, I think it\'s a pretty solid reason to be terrified.
        I\'m not the strongest, not the smartest… It just makes me wonder.
        Why me? Why do get treated this way? Why… Just why… Why did Roman choose me, of all people?
        Why does he want to make my life a living hell? Why do I have to come to school every day, only to have something awful happen…
        The worst part is that I can\'t tell.
        He told me not to tell. He told me never to tell. He said he\'d do something if I did.
        Why. Just why? I snap back to reality when a piece of balled up paper hits my head. Group laughter.
        \n“Pick it up,” a guy laughs. Roman.
    </string>

    <string name = "hospital">
        I wake up in a hospital room, feeling sore and bruised. I\’m wrapped up in bandages, but judging by the looks of things, it\’s not too severe. I don\’t think I\’ve broken anything. My mom is sitting next to the bed, and it looks like she\’s crying. My mom notices that I\’m awake.
        \n“Justin! Oh sweetheart, I thought I had lost you…”
        \nShe takes my hand in hers, and tears start falling down her cheeks. I try to talk, but only a gurgling sound comes out.
        \n“Sweetheart, don\’t talk. The doctors said that your throat is still healing.”
        \nI blink. I must be beaten up pretty bad.
        \n“A nice girl and a boy from your school told a teacher that you were being beat up at that moment, and the teacher stopped the two boys from hurting you even more. They called an ambulance and now you\’re here… The two boys went home, but I\’m going to press charges… My poor baby… I hope you weren\’t hurt too bad...”
        \nShe starts crying again. I roll my eyes to the best of my ability, and I close my hand around hers. She looks up to smile at me, but she still cries.
    </string>

    <string name = "afterHosp">
        I stayed in the hospital for a while. Thankfully, I wasn\’t hurt that badly… I managed a full recovery in a month, but there were some scars left behind. Roman and Dave got expelled, and I never saw them again. The bullying stopped. Vanessa broke up with Dave some time after. Vanessa, Matthew and I became very good friends after that.
    </string>

    <string name = "place">
        I turn around to leave.
        \n“Pick it up,” orders Roman.
        \nI stop in my tracks and pick up the balled up piece of paper.
        \n“Now give it here,” he smiles.
    </string>

    <string name= "SeeWhoThrew">
        I look towards the speaker. As I thought, it\'s Roman. There\'s probably only one person who would bully me. It\'s weird.
        \nI only met him last year, and since then, he\'s decided to pick on me. He doesn\'t really push anyone else around. It\'s just me.
        \nOr maybe he does pick on others too… No one knows that he\'s bullying me, except for his friends… But what are the chances that they\'d do something to help me… If anything, they bully me too.
        \n“What\'re you looking at,” sneers Roman, “Pick it up.”
    </string>

    <string name= "PickUpBall">
        “Now give it here,” smiles Roman.
    </string>

    <string name = "GiveBall">
        I put the ball into his hand.
        \n“Now stand there,” he orders me, pointing at a spot across him.
        \nI stand, looking down, but occasionally looking up. He opens his bag and brings out a roll of duct tape.
        \n“Don\'t move,” he grins.
        \nHe hands the tape to one of his buddies and whispers to him. His buddy smiles and walks towards me, tape in hand. He rips a piece of tape off from the roll and slaps it over my mouth. Then he unravels tape all around me. The tape circles my arms and my bag. I\'m like a tape mummy.
        \n“Come here,” smiles Roman.
        \nI shuffle towards him. He smiles, and takes out a marker from his bag. He writes “STUPID” on the tape binding my arms, then pushes me over. I thrash around. I can\'t get up. He laughs, and gives me a kick.
        \nHis friends do the same thing. Each foot kicks me a bit harder than the last. I writhe in pain, and close my eyes. I just want to cover my head.
        \nI feel so vulnerable… I feel a searing pain on my mouth. Roman has ripped the tape from my mouth.
        \n“Take the tape off, the kid needs to get to class,” he orders his friends, then turning to me, “I\'ll see you at lunch.”
        \nHe walks away, leaving me with his friends. They cut the tape off, cutting pieces of my shirt in the process, and they leave me on the floor with slowly reddening bruises.
    </string>

    <string name ="KeepWalking">
        “Hey, hey Banks, did you not hear me?”
        \nI see him get up from the corner of my eye. I feel afraid. I start running as fast as I can. I hear more laughter.
        \n“Run you dumb turtle. We\'ll see you at lunch,” shouts the guy.
    </string>

    <string name ="FirstPeriodLate">
        I ran into my classroom, panting. Everyone stares at me.
        \n“Justin Banks, why were you late?” asks my teacher.
        \n“I uh, I had to go to the washroom,” I lie, “I wasn\'t feeling well. But I\'m better now.”
        \n“Four more lates, and you\'re going to get detention. Now go take your seat and work on your project until 9:30. Then we\'re going to have a quick lesson.”
        \n“Yes miss.”
        \nClass drifted by like a dream. I felt sore, but it was alright. I was safe in class. Before I knew it, it was second period.
    </string>

    <string name="FirstPeriodOnTime">
        I got to my classroom on time. Thankfully, I\'m not late. I take my seat.
        \n“I\'m going to let you work on your projects today until 9:30, then we\'re going to have a quick lesson.”
        \nClass drifted by like a dream. Before I knew it, it was second period.
    </string>

    <string name ="TravelTime">
        Running to my 2nd period was a hassle. I didn\'t want another late as I have already accumulated 3 lates knowing my science teacher,
        I push myself through the congested hallways or teenagers until I bumped into a wall. I mean. Not a wall. Roman Thanos. He pushes me away, then notices that it\'s me.
        \n“What do you want punk?” he sneers.
    </string>

    <string name="Stutter">
        “Oh really? Then you don\'t mind if I do this?”
        \nHe shoves me against a locker and walks away.
    </string>

    <string name="Stare">
        “What do you want?” he says.
        \nHis voice is starting to develop an agitated tone.
        \n“What you staring at? Get away from me, loser.”
        \nHe walks away from me.
    </string>

    <string name="TurnAround">
        I sprint the opposite direction or Roman and round a corner, panting.
        \nThat was close, I think to myself.
    </string>

    <string name="SecondPeriod">
        *BEEEEP*
        \nI\'m late. I enter the classroom. People are staring at me.
        \n“Sorry I\'m late” I tell my teacher as I quickly walk to my seat.
        \n“Fourth late this month, and it\'s only the 10th. Remember 5 lates is 1 detention,” she says, as I quietly sit down, “We\'re doing a group assignment today, so find a partner.”
        \nI look around. My friend, Jackson, is waving me over. I\'m glad he\'s in my class. I walk to his desk.
        \n“You wanna be partners?” he asks.
    </string>

    <string name="who">
        “Thought you\'d know me by now. I mean, we did only just meet last semester. But I didn\'t think you\'d forget who I am…
        Well, my name\'s Jackson Baker. And coincidentally enough, I like to bake cookies. But video games are fun too. And we\'re friends. Right?”
    </string>

    <string name="no">
        “Well too bad, you\'re working with me, because everyone else is taken,” he grins.
        \n“Okay… So what\'re we doing?”
        \nHe explains all the work and we finish in record time.
        \n“Hey,” he says, in a low whisper, “What do you think of the girl over there?”
        \nHe nods to a goth looking girl.
    </string>

    <string name="pretty">
        “I know right? I think I want to ask her out sometime. I got her number yesterday. Think it\'s worth it?”
        \n“Uh, sure.”
        \nThe bell rang.
        \n“Well, I\'ll text you after school or something,” says Jackson, picking up his things, “I want to talk to her after school, so I won\'t be getting on the bus today.”
        \nThat means that I\'ll be going home alone. I\'ll probably run into Roman. That\'s not good...
        \n“See you around.”
    </string>

    <string name ="creepy">
        “Seriously? Dude, I thought you\'d think better. I think she\'s pretty cute. Like, her eyes. Her hair… I don\'t know, I\'ve honestly never felt like this before about anyone.”
        \n“Okay then...”
        \n“Well anyway, I got her number yesterday, and I want to ask her out sometime. Think it\'s worth a shot?”
        \n“I guess.”
        \nThe bell rings.
        \n“Well I\'ll text you or something,” says Jackson, picking up his things, “I want to talk to her after school, so I won\'t be getting on the bus today.”
        \nThat means that I\'ll be going home alone. I\'ll probably run into Roman. That\'s not good...
        \n“See you around.”
    </string>

    <string name ="sure">
        “I knew you would say that!” he grins, “It\'s not like we have anyone else to work with.”
        \nI sit down beside him. He explains all the work and we finish in record time.
        \n“Hey,” he says, in a low whisper, “What do you think of the girl over there?”
        \nHe nods to a goth looking girl.
    </string>

    <string name="dayOneEnd">
        I exit the school and wait at the bus stop. I can see Roman and his friends outside the school, across the street.
        \nI watch him. He smiles and talks to people. A girl tries to tackle him. I have a feeling she likes him.
        Eventually, he sees me. He doesn\'t do anything. He just turns away and leaves. The bus comes, and I get on. It was a long ride. I arrive home, and I go to my room.
        \nI finally remember the paper ball Roman threw at me. I take it out of my bag.
    </string>

    <string name="ThrowIt">
        I throw it at the most obscure corner in my room. I don\'t need to know what it is, and I don\'t care, either. It\'s his anyway, so I feel a bit better.
        If it\'s really important, then I\'m glad he lost it.
    </string>

    <string name="nextDay">
        I arrived to school, but just as I was about to turn a corner, I heard Roman and his friends\' voices.
        \n“He\'s so gonna get it today,” snarls Roman, “Sometimes, I want to punch that guy in the face so hard that he gets knocked out for days…”
        \nI\'ll admit it, I got scared, and I tiptoed away. I hung around in the library until the bell had rung so then I wouldn\'t run into Roman. First period went by quick.
        \nI hid in the washroom until the second bell had rung, then I sprinted to class. Jackson noticed how I seemed out of breath, but he didn\'t ask me anything.
        \nHe offered me a bag of cookies.
    </string>

    <string name="Accept">
        “Thanks,” I said, taking the bag. I put it in my bag.
        \nTime for third period… But Roman is there.
    </string>

    <string name ="Reject">
        “No thanks,” I said.
        \nHe seemed disappointed.
        Time for third period… But Roman is there.
    </string>

    <string name ="skipClassYC">
        I don\'t think I should go to class. If Roman wants to beat me up, I think I can risk a skip.
        \nI hide in the washroom in the darkest stall. Thankfully, it doesn\'t smell that bad. And it\'s in a quiet wing of the school too, so I don\'t expect many people to be here.
        \nI would have gone to the library instead, but I\'m scared that someone will recognize me and tell me to get to class. 50 minutes until class ends. 40 more minutes. 30 more minutes…
        \nThe door opens and closes, someone comes in. I hear something like a lighter, then a smell of smoke. They push against my stall door, then swear when it\'s not opening. He knocks on the door.
        \n“Yes?” I squeak
        \n“Oh sorry, didn\'t think anyone was here.”
        \nI recognize the voice as Roman\'s.
        \n“It\'s okay,” I manage to say, using a much higher pitched voice.
        \n“Say, who are you?” he asks.
    </string>

    <string name ="lieYC">
        \n“My name\'s Andy…” I lie.
        \n“Well… You wanna come out? You skipping too? Or you taking a dump. Because then I\'m not gonna bother you.”
        \n“Uh… I\'m uh… Just here.”
        \n“Skipping then,” he smirks, “Want a smoke?”
        \n“You\'re not supposed to smoke in school…”
        \n“Screw it. My life, my rules.”
        \n“Why\'re you like this?” I venture.
        \n“Messed up family, messed up friends, messed up me,” he chuckles, “Just saying, I don\'t usually talk with strangers in bathroom stalls. If you wondered.”
        \n“Ah… No, I didn\'t... “
        \n“Well… Life\'s been sh*tty. Like this washroom. Ha, ha… Get it? No? Okay…”
        \n“Uh I got it. But it was a really bad joke. Sorry.”
        \n“Say… You sound really familiar. You remind me of one of the kids from middle school. That kid was a crazy good baker man... I can\'t really put my finger on him right now, but he goes to our school.“
        \n“Wait, do you mean Jackson Baker?!”
        \n“I think so, yeah. I remember his last name. I\'d kill for one of his cookies right now.”
    </string>

    <string name ="skipClassNC">
        \nI don\'t think I should go to class. If Roman wants to beat me up, I think I can risk a skip.
        \nI hide in the washroom in the darkest stall. Thankfully, it doesn\'t smell that bad. And it\'s in a quiet wing of the school too, so I don\'t expect many people to be here.
        \nI would have gone to the library instead, but I\'m scared that someone will recognize me and tell me to get to class. 50 minutes until class ends. 40 more minutes. 30 more minutes…
        \nThe door opens and closes, someone comes in. I hear something like a lighter, then a smell of smoke. They push against my stall door, then swear when it\'s not opening. He knocks on the door.
        \n“Yes?” I squeak.
        \n“Oh sorry, didn\'t think anyone was here.”
        \nI recognize the voice as Roman\'s.
        \n“It\'s okay,” I manage to say, using a much higher pitched voice.
        \n“Say, who are you?” he asks, “I\'m Roman Thanos.”
    </string>

    <string name ="tellTheTruthNC">
        “It\'s Justin Banks,” I mutter.
        \n“Sorry, what?”
        \n“I\'m Justin. Justin Banks?” I say, louder.
        \n“Justin Banks… Not ringing any bells. Wanna come out? I\'ll recognize you then.”
        \n“Uh…”
    </string>

    <string name ="lieNC">
        “My name\'s Andy…” I lie.
        \n“Well… You wanna come out? You skipping too? Or you taking a dump. Because then I\'m not gonna bother you.”
        \n“Uh… I\'m uh… Just here.”
        \n“Skipping then,” he smirks, “Want a smoke?”
        \n“You\'re not supposed to smoke in school…”
        \n“Screw it. My life, my rules.”
        \n“Why\'re you like this?” I venture.
        \n“Messed up family, messed up friends, messed up me,” he chuckles, “Just saying, I don\'t usually talk with strangers in bathroom stalls. If you wondered.”
        \n“Ah… No, I didn\'t... “
        \n“Well… Life\'s been sh*tty. Like this washroom. Ha, ha… Get it? No? Okay…”
        \n“Uh I got it. But it was a really bad joke. Sorry.”
        \n“Say… You sound really familiar. You remind me of one of the kids from middle school. That kid was a crazy good baker man... I can\'t really put my finger on him right now, but he goes to our school.“
        \n“Wait, do you mean Jackson Baker?!”
        \n“I think so, yeah. I remember his last name. I\'d kill for one of his cookies right now.”
        \n“Sorry man, I don\'t have any.”
        \n“Hey, are you friends with Baker?”
        \n“Yeah...”
        \n“Can you get him to come meet me after school?”
    </string>

    <string name="noCanDo">
        “I\'m sorry, but I\'m not going to do that for someone I just met. And we met under very strange circumstances too…”
        \n“True that. Well it was nice talking, Andy. If you ever change your mind, tell him to find me in front of the school near the trees.”
        \nI hear footsteps and the door opening and closing. I look at my watch. The bell\'s about to ring for lunch. I leave the washrooms and I go find Jackson.
    </string>

    <string name="lunchBuddies">
        I text Jackson to come find me at the bench in the English hallway. Were technically not supposed to eat in the hallways, but it feels like no one really cares. Jackson\'s already there when I arrive.
        \n“How long have you known Roman?” I ask Jackson.
        \n“A while. Ever since middle school.”
        \n“What was he like?”
        \n“Well… He was always pretending to be a tough guy… But it never worked. He was too nice. And he was a bit of a nerd. Star Trek club. And now, he\'s a bit of a jerk, according to some people. I kind of wonder what happened to him sometimes. But why do you want to know all of this? You don\'t seem like the kind of guy who would ever talk to him.”
        \n“He mentioned that he would do anything for one of your cookies.”
        \n“He remembers..? Wow… I\'d gladly give him some. I still have the bag of cookies you rejected.”
        \n“I don\'t think he deserves anything from you. You\'re a good guy. Why would you give him anything good?”
        \n“Wow… That really came out of nowhere. Something wrong?”
    </string>

    <string name ="stayIn">
        “I\'m just going to stay in here,” I reply.
        \n“You\'re a weird kid, aren\'t you,” he snickers.
        \n“What do you mean?”
        \n“Wait. You\'re not a weird kid, you\'re the weird kid.”
        \n“What?”
        \n“You\'re the kid!”
        \n“How do you know?”
        \n“Oh boy… Wait till the others hear about this!”
        \nI can almost hear the laugh in his voice.
        \n“Well Justin,” he continues, “You\'re in luck. We\'ve got something big going on after school today. And you\'re going to be there. Meet us at the trees in front of school. And if you don\'t come…”
        \nHe lets the threat hang in the air. After a pause, he adds, “See you there.”
        \nI hear the door open and close. Skipping was a bad idea. I should have just gone to class…

    </string>

    <string name="comeOut">
        I walk out of the stall. Roman looks surprised.
        \n“Hey, it\'s you,” he says.
        \n“It\'s me…” I mutter.
        \n“Thought you were too much of a goody two-shoes to skip anything,” he smirks.
        \nI look at my shoes.
        \n“Looks like I was wrong,” he continues, oblivious to my silence, “Maybe you can help me with something after school. Come find me and the others at the trees in front of school. And if you don\'t come...”
        \nHe lets the threat hang in the air for a while before turning to the door.
        \n“See you, Banks,” he smiles, and he leaves the washrooms.
    </string>

    <string name ="noCookies">
        “Sorry man, I don\'t have any.”
        \n“Hey, are you friends with Baker?”
        \n“Yeah...”
        \n“Can you get him to come meet me after school?”
    </string>

    <string name ="illDoIt">
    \n“I\'ll do it,” I say.
    \nI don\'t know why I agreed to this, but I probably have to keep up this ‘Andy\' thing up for a while.
    \n“Thanks man, you\'re the best,” he replies.
    \nI can hear the smile in his voice. Are Jackson\'s cookies really that good?! I sort of regret passing up on them.
    \n“Third\'s almost over by the way. Thanks for the talk. And if you tell any of my friends that I\'ve been talking to randos in washrooms, I\'m gonna punch you,” he laughs.
    \nNot sure if he\'s being serious about punching me, but I\'m definitely not going to risk it.
    </string>

    <string name ="stopHim">
    “No, don\'t,” I say.
    \n“Why not? The guy\'s been pushing you around like a rag doll…”
    \n“I don\'t know, but please… Don\'t do it…”
    \n“Fine. Then let\'s go together to meet him. I\'m going to put him in his place.”
    \n“You\'re going to beat him up?! But that\'s -”
    \n“No, silly, I\'m just going to give him an old run of the Baker tongue.”
    \n“Ew.”
    \n“It means I\'m going to talk to him, geez.”
    \n“Alright…”
    \n“So what do you think? You want to come with me?”
    </string>

    <string name="noConfront">
    “I\'d prefer not go to,” I reply.
    \n“Why not?”
    \n“I don\'t want him finding me and yeah…”
    \n“Reasonable. Alright then, I\'ll go alone. Do you know where he wants me to meet him?”
    \n“No… But he usually hangs out by the trees in the front of school.”
    \n“Alright then. I\'ll go there. Bell\'s about to ring. Peace out.”
    </string>

    <string name="afterSchool_3">
    After that day, I never saw much of Roman again, except in class. But eventually, he transferred out of that class, and I never really did see him again. I\'ve caught glimpses of someone who looked like him here and there, but nothing more.
        \nThe bullying has stopped, but I sometimes see Roman\'s friends looking at me and laughing. Even though there\'s a pretty big chance that they\'re not talking about me, there\'s always a slim chance.
        \nJackson never said much about what happened. I\'m just glad it\'s over, for the most part.

    </string>

    <string name="confront">
    “Of course I\'d want to go with you,” I reply, “If he starts acting up, then it\'ll be a two against one.”
    \n“Fighting isn\'t necessary, young grasshopper,” he jokes.
    \n“Sometimes it is,” I object.
    \n“That\'s irrelevant. I\'ll see you after school then. Do you know where he wanted to meet up?”
    \n“Uh… No. But I know where he usually hangs out after school. Mainly because I have to avoid it...”
    \n“Alright then, we\'ll go there”
    </string>

    <string name ="theConfrontation">
    I meet up with Jackson after school, and we go to the trees in front of school. Sure enough, Roman is there, but his gang of friends aren\'t with him. He recognises me, and I can feel myself shrinking slowly. Jackson keeps me going.
    \n“Hello Banks,” says Roman, tipping an imaginary hat, “And… Jackson?”
    \n“The one and only,” smiles Jackson.
    \nHis smile has no friendliness in it.
    \n“What do you want?” asks Jackson.
    \n“Nothing much really. Now that I look at it, it seems so stupid…” sighs Roman.
    \n“What do you want?!” snaps Jackson.
    \n“Chill… I just want a… I want a cookie…” says Roman.
    \nJackson relaxes immediately, and gives Roman a bag of cookies.
    \n“Thanks dude. I appreciate it,” says Roman, taking a cookie out of the bag.
    \n“How\'s life?” asks Jackson.
    \n“Not the best,” Roman replies.
    \nThey keep small talking, acting like I\'m not there. I can\'t say I mind, but it bugs me a little. I blank out for a while until I realize that Roman and Jackson are looking at me, both expecting an answer.
    \n“Sorry, what?” I ask.
    \n“Roman asked if you\'d forgive him,” explains Jackson.
    \n“I just… Life\'s been rough on me… It\'s my family… And I feel like I\'ve been unleashing all my anger at you. So I\'m sorry for that. Will you forgive me?”
    </string>

    <string name="doNotForgive">
    “I won\'t.”
    \nRoman looks worried.
    \n“Why not?” he asks.
    \n“You\'ve hurt me too much… You know, it\'s super hard to forgive someone right off the bat like this, you know?”
    \n“Yeah… I know exactly how you feel… My mom\'s… I don\'t know, I think he\'s her boyfriend? Well… He bullies me… And to be honest, if he asked me to forgive him, I\'d never do it. It\'s alright though. I understand.”
    \n“Sorry about that.”
    \n“No problem. I\'ll stop bothering you then.”
    \nRoman stayed true to his word. He stopped going after me, and whenever his friends wanted to come over, he\'d stop them. I\'m glad he\'s stopped, and I\'m mostly glad that it\'s over.

    </string>

    <string name="forgiveYou">
    I FORGIVE YOU
    “I forgive you,” I reply.
    \nHe looks really relieved.
    \n“Really?”
    \n“Yeah. Just don\'t do it again.”
    \nLame. I should have thought of something better to say.
    \n“I won\'t. I promise.”
    \nRoman looks so happy. Jackson also looks pretty happy. I wonder what they talked about…
    \nAfter that day, Roman didn\'t bother me that much. He nods to me in the hallway sometimes, but other than that, our interactions are kept at a minimum. I\'m glad it\'s all over.

    </string>

    <string name="encourageHim">
    ENCOURAGE HIM
    \n“Really? You\'d do that?” I ask.
    \n“I would do anything for a friend. Well, almost anything. But I really can\'t just sit here and watch as you get beat up or whatever… It just feels wrong.”
    \n“Thank you so much,” I say, my eyes filling up with tears of gratefulness.
    \n“No problem. I\'m going to do it after school.”
    </string>

    <string name="day2">
    The next day, I get called down to the vice principal\'s office during class. I am asked about whether or not I was bullied. I tell them everything. Jackson tells me that he too had been called down and questioned. I don\'t know what happened to Roman, but I didn\'t see him for some time afterwards. There were rumours that he got suspended, then he changed schools. I don\'t know what to believe, but I\'m just glad that it\'s over.

    </string>

    <string name="openIt">
    I open up the crumpled ball. It\'s an utility bill. Why would he carry something important like this around?!
    \n“Jennifer Thorne...” I read.
    \nI\'m pretty sure Roman\'s last name is Thanos, not Thorne… I check in my yearbook just to make sure. Yep, it\'s Thanos. Weird. I thought Roman lived with his parents, like everyone else. Not with some random lady. But… What if he stole that bill from her? What if he\'s terrorizing innocent people from the community too, and not just me?
    </string>

    <string name="textJackson">
    I pull out my phone to text Jackson. After all, that\'s what friends are for, right? I send him a text.
    \nHey Jackson, do you know Roman?
    \nYa, y?
    \nWhat\'s his mom\'s name?
    \nDude that\'s weird af
    \nLook, I just need to know her name
    \ny?
    \nBecause I have a letter for Jennifer Thorne, and I\'m pretty sure that\'s not his mom
    \nLol ik his mom\'s name is Jennifer but idk bout the last name
    \nThanks anyway
    \nNP man.
    \nWell, even if that\'s his mom, it still doesn\'t explain anything, like why Roman would have that in his bag.
    </string>

    <string name="notDoAnything">
    I don\'t want to get involved. Besides, if I told anyone about it, Roman would come and hurt me… Or even worse… I\'m so scared. I\'ll pretend nothing happened.
    </string>

    <string name="goToHouse">
    No harm in visiting her, right? I do have her address after all… It\'s surprisingly close. Maybe half an hour by bike. Maybe less. And my parents won\'t be home until late tonight. They\'re always out doing work. I\'ll just leave a note…
    \nI get my bike out of the garage. It\'s spring, so it\'s still light outside. I don\'t have any homework, or upcoming tests or quizzes or anything like that that needs immediate attention.
    \nI bike all the way there, and I arrive. The house looks a little run down, even though it\'s in the seemingly nice part of the neighbourhood. To be honest, I have no idea why I\'m here.
    \nI hear someone coming. I hide between a bush and the wooden fence that marks the property lines. My bike is on the ground. I hope whoever it is can\'t see me.
    \n“Who are you, and why are you hiding?” I hear.
    \nIt\'s a man, maybe in his late forties. He looks very unkempt. Also, he reeks.
    \n“I… I\'m looking for someone...” I stutter.
    \n“Who?”
    </string>

    <string name="sayJennifer">
        “JENNIFER”
        \n“You\'re looking for Jennifer? My Jennifer?!”
        \n“I don\'t know!” I stammer, “Jennifer Thorne!”
        \n“Not… Jennifer Thanos. Not that disgusting… Name...”
        \n“Yes.”
        \n“Well what are you doing here, snooping out on our front lawn like this?!”
        \n\n“I… I dropped my bike!”
        \n“What, did Roman give you something to give his mother? Did he? Give me the note!”
        \n\n“I don\'t have a note!”
        \n“You\'re lying! You have that piece of paper right there-”
        \n“Larry!” shrills a woman\'s voice.
        \n“Jennifer, do you know this boy? He says he\'s looking for you. He\'s also got a note in his hand...”
        \n“Well... May I speak with the boy?” she asks him.
        \n“No.”
        \n“But Larry, I-”
        \n“NO!”
        \n“But-”
        \n“Who\'s paying the bills, who\'s keeping the house warm, who\'s keeping the electricity running, who\'s-”
        \n“I\'m sorry,” she sobs, dark lines streaking down her makeuped face.
        \n“You\'d better be!”
        \nHe storms inside, leaving her sobbing quietly in the doorway. She reaches in and scrawls something down on a small piece of paper, then throws outside. She gives me one last fearful look, then she shuts the door with a silent click.
    </string>

    <string name="sayRoman">
        “You\'re looking for Roman?! Who are you? His friend? Doesn\'t he know that he\'s not allowed to have friends over?”
        \nHis face goes from pale to tomato red in a matter of seconds.
        \n“Sorry sir! I didn\'t know!” I stammer.
        \n“Damn right you didn\'t,” he snarls.
        \n“I just… I wanted to surprise him. He doesn\'t know I\'m here.”
        \n“Well he ain\'t here!” he roars, “I kicked him out of this house, that disgraceful son of a-”
        \n“Larry!” says a woman\'s voice from the doorway.
        \nHis face becomes normal in seconds.
        \n“Jennifer!” he smiles.
        \nShe walks over to him in her slippers.
        \n“Come on inside, baby… It\'s so cold...”
        \n“But this kid-”
        \n“Don\'t bother with that little brat over there. He\'s one of the… Uh… Autistic neighbourhood kids. He probably thinks everyone is his friend. Poor boy will never learn. Come, come...”
        \nShe takes him by the arm and leads him into the house. She then scrawls something on a piece of paper and throws it out. She gives me a panicked look before shutting the door with a quiet click. I pick up the note. I don\'t know what happened, but… Roman\'s probably with his friends. I\'m starting to feel bad for him. Forget about my situation… If I ever had to face Larry, I\'d probably be dead.
    </string>

    <string name="nextDayVisited">
        The next day, I have the note in my pocket. I know I\'m going to run into Roman at some point in time, but I don\'t know when. I\'m going to give him the note. I hope the note doesn\'t say anything about me… But you know, maybe I should look at the note… Just to see what it says…
    </string>

    <string name="notReadNote">
        It\'s none of my business anyway. I should probably find Roman now…
        I walk down the hallway, and I see Roman\'s friend.
        \n“Excuse me…” I say, tapping his shoulder.
        \nHe turns around and breaks into a smile.
        \n“Well… Hello there,” he grins.
        \n“Hi, I was wondering if you knew where Roman was…”
        \n“Sorry, I have no idea. He was supposed to be here five minutes ago… Nice bag,” he laughs, “I wonder if there\'s anything good in it.”
        \nHe snatches my bag and tries to yank it up. Fortunately, we\'re about the same height, so nothing really happens. And my bag is really heavy, so that\'s a plus. I see Roman walking towards us.
        \n“Hey Dave, what\'re you doing?” asks Roman.
        \n“Just trying to play with this kid,” he replies, “He\'s looking for you by the way.”
        \n“What do you want?” asks Roman.
        \n“I have something for you from Jenn-”
        \n“Hey Dave, can you leave us alone for a bit?”
        \n“Sure, anything.”
        \nDave pushes past me and leaves.
        \n“You have something from my mom?” asks Roman, “How did you get something from my mom?!”
        \n“I uh… Went to your house yesterday. And she gave me this note…”
        \nI give him the note.
        \n“Did you read it?” he asks.
        \n“No. I figured that it was personal or something so…”
        \n“And going to my house is definitely not personal.”
        \n“Sorry…”
        \n“How do you even know where I live anyway.?”
        \n“You threw a paper with your address on it at me…”
        \n“Oh… Sorry about that.”
        \nHe looks pretty upset.
        \n“Your family situation sucks.”
        \n“You met Larry, didn\'t you.”
        \n“He like, bullies your mom… He\'s scary.”
        \n“You haven\'t seen him drunk yet. That\'s when the demon is unleashed from hell.”
        \n“I… Wow, that must be awful…”
        \n“Yeah man. Geez… I want to talk more and stuff but… Bell\'s about to ring. And you\'re a goody two shoes. Can\'t have you be late. So… Talk to you later, maybe… Or actually, do you want to meet up somewhere? I just… Need to get something off my chest.”
        \n“Uh… Okay?”
        \n“4:00 pm, Rollingston Park. I\'m going alone, since my friends are… They\'re just a bit weird, and I don\'t think they\'d want to talk about my situation. Like, they all have their own problems and stuff, so I\'d rather not bother them.”
        \n“Um…”
        \n“Wait, do I scare you?”
        \n“Uh…”
        \n“I probably do… You can bring your friends if you want. I don\'t mind. But get the friends you trust because I don\'t want to be sweeping up your loose ends.”
        \n“Uh… Okay…”
        \n“See you then. Get to class. You\'re going to be late if you don\'t.”
    </string>

    <string name="readNote">
        I should have read it yesterday when I had the chance. I unfold it. I feel guilty, like I\'m looking at something that I shouldn\'t be looking at. Which I technically am.
        \n Roman, I\'m going to kick Larry out of the house. I\'ve had enough of him and his mean and hurtful words. I\'m sorry you had to see him be mean to you. I hope you\'re doing alright. Come back home… I miss you. Love, Mom.
        \nI fold it back up. That guy\'s family has got some major problems. I shouldn\'t have been so quick to judge… Now I feel bad. I attempt to shove the note back into my pocket, but someone catches my wrist.
        \n“What\'s that in your hand? A love letter?”
        \nIt\'s not Roman. It\'s his friend. I don\'t know who this guy is, but he follows him around everywhere, almost like a personal waiter.
        \n“None of your business,” I say, trying to wrench my wrist from his grasp.
        \n“Give it,” he smirks, snatching the paper from me and trying to read it.
        \n“Hey! Stop it!” I shout, trying to take it back.
        \n“Dave! Quit it!” exclaims a familiar voice.
        \nDave stops and we both turn to see Roman.
        \n“But—” Dave protests.
        \n“I\'m the only one who should be shoving this squeaker around, not you. Got it?”
        \n“Yeah yeah… But he\'s got a note, Rome! I think you should read it,” he smiles, handing over the note to him, “Bet it\'s a cheesy love letter to some useless girl.”
        \nRoman opens up the note, and reads it. His eyes narrow.
        \n“Where did you get this?” he asks.
        \n“I went to your h—”
        \n“Dave get out of here, I want to talk to this kid one on one,” interrupts Roman, throwing a mean look to Dave.
        \nDave nods, scared, and he walks away, cursing and muttering under his breath.
        \n“So you went to my house,” says Roman.
        \n“Yeah, and—”
        \n“And my mother gave this to you.”
        \n“Not really, she actually threw it out—”
        \n“So she threw it out the window. That\'s all I am to her. Just another thing that can get thrown out a window.”
        \n“Will you please just listen?!” I snap.
        \nImmediately, I regret my harsh tone. His eyes are angry.
        \n“I\'m sorry,” I whisper.
        \n“No, no… Don\'t be… I shouldn\'t have been like that. Let\'s start from the beginning. Why did you go to my house? And how do you even know where I live? Creepy stalker.”
        \n“Uh… You know that paper you threw at me yesterday…”
        \n“Old utility bill. Right.”
        \n“Well I decided to check the place out, and uh... Larry yelled at me for going to your house, and then Jennifer came outside and bought Larry back in and then she wrote it and threw it outside so I picked it up.”
        \n“You read it, didn\'t you.”
    </string>

    <string name="sayNo">
        “Liar. Then how did you know to give it to me?”
        \n“I\'m sorry! I just didn\'t want you to be mad at me… I\'m sorry...”
        \n“Man… Am I really that screwed up...”
        \n“It\'s just that… I was curious...”
        \n“Curiosity killed the cat,” he remarks dryly.
        \n“I\'m sorry,” I reply, ashamed at my lie.
        \n“Look man, let\'s meet up sometime tonight. I guess I just need someone to talk to.”
        \n“Um… Well...”
        \n“Still don\'t trust me? Bring someone with you if you want. I\'ll understand.”
        \n“I have a curfew at seven...”
        \n“Fine. Four in the afternoon on the school roof. Know how to get there?”
        \n“That\'s dangerous.”
        \n“Fine. You know Rollingston Park? It\'s right near here.”
        \n“I\'ll search it up.”
        \n“Cool, see you then.”
        \nThe bell rings and he leaves. Time to go to class.
    </string>

    <string name="sayYes">
        “Well… Dang. Do you want to meet up sometime tonight? I don\'t know… I guess I just need someone to talk to.”
        \n“Um… I… Uh…”
        \n“Bring someone with you if you want. I understand. I probably terrify you.”
        \n“Uh… But I need to be home by seven.”
        \n“‘Kay. Four in the afternoon?”
        \n“Um… Sure…”
        \n“Alright. I\'ll be on the roof of the Glass Piazza. You know how to get there?”
        \n“That\'s dangerous.”
        \n“Fine, then the park. Rollingston Park. It\'s right near here.”
        \n“Uh… I\'ll search it up.”
        \n“Cool, see you there then.”
        \nThe bell rings and he leaves. Time to go to class.
    </string>

    <string name ="classTime">
        Jackson has saved me a seat. Once I sit down, he immediately starts talking.
        \n“Hey Justin, I asked around, and turns out Roman\'s mom is named Jennifer Thanos… But she changed it back to her maiden name, Thorne, after her husband left her to take care of Roman…”
        \n“Dang… How did you even find all this information?!”
        \n“Internet.”
        \n“Not buying it. Creepy stalker.”
        \nHe smiles, and elbows me sharply.
        \n“Violet\'s my girlfriend now,” he smiles.
        \n“Who\'s Violet?”
        \n“The girl. Remember?”
        \n“Now I do. Just wondering, do you have time today? After school at four.”
        \n“Sure, why?”
        \n“Roman asked me to meet him at Rollingston Park, and I was wondering if you knew where it was.”
        \n“Yeah, I live near there.”
        \n“Can you come with me? Like, show me where it is and all that.”
        \n“Sure, why not.”
    </string>

    <string name="afterSchoolWalking">
    After school, Jackson and I meet outside school.
    \n“So you know where this park is, right?” I ask.
    \n“Yep. It\'s within walking distance anyway. By the way, why\'re you meeting up with Roman? He doesn\'t seem like someone you\'d hang out with. And I\'ve never seen you talk to him either. In fact… Sorry for being so direct, but it seemed like you were avoiding him all the time.”
    </string>

    <string name="tellALie">
    “Did it seem like I was avoiding him?” I ask.
    \n“Yeah. Like you\'d look both ways before you cross a hallway. And you kinda run away from him when he\'s near. That stuff.”
    \n“Well… It wasn\'t on purpose. If that\'s what you think. Um… I guess we\'re friends. Sort of. But we just don\'t really talk.”
    \n“I\'m on the same boat… We used to be friends, but then everything changed. Alright. I don\'t know. But how did you guys decide to meet up then?”
    \n“He just wanted to talk. You know. Bro to bro?”
    \n“And I\'m your GPS?”
    \n“Mainly.”
    \n“Well… The park\'s right there,” he says, gesturing ahead.
    \nI can vaguely see Roman sitting on a swing.
    </string>

    <string name="jacksonLeaves">
    “Hey, thanks for showing me the way man, but I\'m here for a one on one with him,” I say.
    \n“A fight?!”
    \n“No, a talk. He needed someone to talk to, and I said I\'d be there for him.”
    \n“Oh I see… So it\'s sort of personal. No matter, I live right there anyway. I\'ll get going then. Later,” he says, starting off in another direction.
    \nI watch him go down a block and then I go to Roman.
    \n“You came here alone?” asks Roman.
    \n“Jackson came with me to show me the way, but then he went home.”
    \n“Which Jackson? Jackson Baker?”
    \n“Yeah him.”
    \n“Shame… I would have wanted to talk to him too. We used to know each other back in middle school.”
    \n“Really?”
    \n“Yeah. Star Trek Club. We were complete nerds… But at least life was better then.”
    \n“That\'s… Interesting…”
    \n“So uh… I called you here so then I could apologize. Like, I\'ve been… I\'ve been bullying you. And to be honest, it\'s not my fault. Actually, it\'s technically all my fault. But I\'ve been having family problems and all that jazz. I got angry and stuff, but like… I guess I channeled my anger into you instead. I\'m really sorry about that, and if there\'s anything I can do to make up to you… I\'ll do it.”
    </string>

    <string name="forgiveHim">
        “Well there is one thing…” I start.
        \n“What is it?” he asks.
        \n“Be my friend. We can start from there instead.”
        \n“You sure about that..?” he asks.
        \n“Yeah. Instead of making bad memories, we can replace them with good ones. And I feel like you\'re being sincere and all that… So… If you don\'t mind, maybe we can be friends!”
        \n“I… Yeah, let\'s be friends. I\'m still sorry that I-”
        \n“Drop it. Let it go. I don\'t care. The past is gone, okay? We should start from the beginning.”
        \nI stick out my hand.
        \n“Hi, my name is Justin Banks. What\'s your name?”
        \n“I\'m Roman Thanos,” he smiles, taking my hand in a firm grasp.
        \n“Pleased to meet you,” I smile, “So… What do you like to do?”
    </string>

    <string name="notForgiveHim">
        “No.”
        \n“Sorry, what?” he frowns.
        \n“There\'s nothing you can do to make up for the damage you\'ve done. I appreciate you defending me against that other guy, but… I don\'t think I can trust you yet. For all I care, you could be luring me into a trap.”
        \n“I\'d never do that.”
        \n“But you have the capability. So… I\'m sorry, but I can\'t forgive you yet.”
        \n“It\'s alright. I guess I just won\'t bother you again...”
        \nRoman gets up and leaves. I\'m relieved. I don\'t have to deal with him any more. I\'m free…
    </string>

    <string name="afterSchool_2">
        When school ends, I go to the trees in front of school. Roman and his friends are already there, waiting for me. Roman smiles and waves when he sees me approaching.
        \n“And here is our special guest, Mr. Justin Banks!” he proclaims with an exaggerated bravado.
        \nHis friends laugh and applaud. One girl looks concerned.
        \n“Are you sure we should do this?” she asks.
        \n“Are you chicken?” he asks.
        \n“No, but I really don\'t think-”
        \n“Look Vanessa, if you don\'t want to go with the plan, then just get outta here. No one wants you anyway, except this piece of trash,” he laughs, lightly shoving the boy next to her.
        \n“He\'s more of a man than you\'ll ever be,” says Vanessa, her voice developing a frigid tone, “Come on, Dave.”
        \n“But Vanessa…” protests the guy that got shoved.
        \n“Fine! Be that way! Ugh!” she replies, and she walks away.
        \nAnother one of Roman\'s friends follows her away.
        \n“Dave… Why do you even date that girl…” groans Roman.
        \n“She\'s a one of a kind beauty,” replies the guy that got shoved, Dave.
        \nRoman rolls his eyes. Then he grabs my backpack roughly and drags me further away into the school parking lot. Everyone knows that the parking lot doesn\'t have security cameras monitoring it, since our school is too poor to afford a decent security system.
        \n“We\'re going to have some fun, Justin. It\'s a shame that those two had to leave…”
        \nHe pushes me roughly and I fall flat on the asphalt. Pain shoots through my hands, and I notice that they\'re bleeding.
        \n“Get up,” urges Roman.
        \n“Get up,” echoes Dave.
        \nI struggle to my feet, only to be thrown down by Dave. They laugh. They tell me to get up, only to push me down again. I feel worthless. I feel used. Why do I have to go through all of this?
        \nFinally, they get bored of me, and they start throwing punches and kicks at me. The pain is unbearable.
        \n“Stop…” I whisper.
        \nA final kick fills my mouth with blood, and sends me into the painless realm of unconsciousness.
    </string>

    <string name="jacksonStays">
        “Roman!” shouts Jackson.
        \nHe looks up and waves half-heartedly. We go stand in front of him.
        \n“Jackson? Haven\'t seen you in ages. How you been?” asks Roman.
        \n“Got me a girlfriend, and I\'ve been good,” he replies smugly.
        \n“Hey Justin,” nods Roman.
        \n“Hey,” I reply.
        \n “So… Um… I just wanted someone to talk to. Someone I could trust, I guess. Because to be honest, none of my friends are really… Like, they\'re good people, but I just… Argh! Look, Justin, I\'m sorry for everything, okay? I\'m sorry for all the times I\'ve made fun of you, pushed you in lockers, everything! I don\'t care any more, but life is just stressing me out…”
        \n“Justin?!” exclaims Jackson, shocked, “You said you were… Okay you know what? We need to talk about this later.”
        \n“It\'s okay, really! The past is in the past… Let it go,” I tell Roman.
        \n“You sure about that?”
        \n“Yeah, uh, we can be friends!” I exclaim.
        \n“Aren\'t you already…” starts Jackson.
        \n“Are you sure you want to be friends with me?” questions Roman, “I\'ve been pretty awful to you and stuff…”
        \n“Of course!” I reply.
        \nJackson pulls me aside.
        \n“You\'re a terrible person, Justin. I just want to get one thing straight. And I\'m not talking about Roman, I\'m talking about your lying. Like, why would you do that?!”
        \n“I was scared what you\'d think…”
        \n“Look, we\'re friends, so I\'d look out for you no matter what. But lying to me just sort of dissolves our bond. I know we aren\    \'t that close, but was a lie really necessary?!”
        \n“No but-”
        \n“Oh gosh, I\'m losing my temper. Sorry man, I just don\'t really… Appreciate you\'re lying. Though to be honest, it wasn\'t really convincing. And Roman confirmed the lie.”
        \n“You two done yet?” asks Roman, looking annoyed.
        \n“Yeah, just shoving some morals into my friend,” replies Jackson, putting emphasis on the word friend.
        \n“Was that necessary?” asks Roman.
        \n“Whatever. I\'m just being a bit of a wet blanket. I\'ll be fine in a bit,” he assures.
        \n“Well… Alright then. So we\'re friends?” asks Roman, holding up a fist.
        \n“Yeah…”
        \nI give him a fist bump. I feel like Jackson will be fine afterwards. I\'m mostly glad that I just made a friend.
    </string>

    <string name="tellHimTheTruth">
        “Can you keep a secret?” I ask.
        \n“Sure? What is it?” he asks, suddenly looking concerned.
        \n“Um… He… He used to make fun of me. And push me around.”
        \n“So he\'s a bully.”
        \n“No! I mean yes… But I just took it.”
        \n“Should have stood up for yourself.”
        \n“I was scared… I don\'t know. What could I have done?”
        \n“So why\'re you meeting up with him?!”
        \n“Because he wants to talk… He comes from a really bad family, apparently, and he… He stood up for me this morning. His friend was trying to take something from me, and he told him to back off. He just had a change of heart or something. I don\'t know. But I agreed to meet up with him. He said I could bring a friend if I needed one.”
        \n“Dude… That\'s weird.”
        \n“But still.”
        \n“Well… I\'m glad you\'re alright. It\'s really great that you stood up for yourself. I\'m proud of you.”
        \n“Thanks dad.”
        \n“Justin.”
        \n“What?”
        \n“I. Am. Not. Your. Father!”
        \nWe laugh.
    </string>

    <string name = "dontGiveCookie">
        Why would I ever give him a cookie? They\’re mine!
        \n“Sorry, I don\’t have any right now,” I lie.
        \n“Shame. Hey, are you friends with Jackson Baker?”
        \n“Yeah?”
        \n“Could you tell him to come find me after school?”
    </string>

    <string name="atThePark">
        We arrive at the park. Roman is already there, sitting on the swings alone with his earphones plugged into his ears. I wave at him. He gives me a small smile.
        \n“Hey,” he says, raising his hand.
        \n“Hi,” I reply.
        \n“Jackson?!”
        \n“Yeah. This is Jackson.”
        \n“Hey Rome,” says Jackson, saluting him with a strange hand gesture.
        \n“Jackie,” he nods, returning the salute.
        \n“You guys know each other..?!” I exclaim, bewildered.
        \n“Middle school,” explains Roman.
        \n“Yeah… We were in the same club. Some Star Trek thing,” smiles Jackson, “You wouldn\'t know. But high school kind of changed everything. Like, we barely speak with each other. Or see each other, for that fact,” he sighs, then he turns to Roman and says, “Justin asked me to come with him to the park. So I wondered, why did you ask Justin to come?”
        \n“I just wanted someone to talk to,” explains Roman, “Life\'s been rough. And I\'m not proud to say it, but I\'ve been mean to him. Not just once. I kind of… I kind of channeled my anger into him. I\'m pretty sure he\'s terrified of me. So I thought that maybe he could bring a friend. Someone he could trust. I\'m kind of glad it\'s you.”
        \n“I see... I\'m glad that you\'ve made up with him. He told me about that already, but I needed to hear it from you.”
        \n“You don\'t trust me?!” I ask, feigning shock.
        \n“Of course not,” laughs Jackson.
        \n“Are you scared of me?” asks Roman.
        \n“Not really,” I reply, “Your family situation is kind of terrible.”
        \n“It\'s hell,” he replies, “But I\'m actually pretty happy that I\'m not terrifying. I\'m sorry about everything, and I know I can\'t make everything up to you, but… I don\'t know. So… Do you want to be friends?”
    </string>

    <string name="becomeFriends">
        “Yes. Let\'s be friends,” I reply, sticking out my hand.
        \nHe shakes it. He looks relieved.
        \n“Great. I\'m glad we can be friends.”
        \n“Can I join in on the friendship?” jokes Jackson.
        \n“Only if you have those legendary cookies,” grins Roman.
        \n“You still remember my cookies…” smiles Jackson, “Of course I have them. I was going to give them to Violet, but she\'s apparently allergic to one of the ingredients.”
        \nHe pulls out a bag of cookies from his bag, and hands them to Roman. He takes one and passes the bag to me.
        \n“Take one,” he says, “They\'re really good.”
        \n“Thanks,” I reply, taking a cookie.
        \nI bite into it. It\'s delicious.
        \n“Three cheers for friendship!” shouts Jackson.
        \n“That\'s really tacky,” I reply, my voice muffled by a cookie.
        \n“HIP HIP, HURRAY!” shouts Jackson and Roman.
        \n“I can\'t believe you did that,” I laugh.
        \n“I\'d do anything for a friend,” smiles Roman.
    </string>

    <string name="notFriends">
        “No. I can\'t. I\'m sorry,” I reply.
        \nIt\'s not his fault. It\'s mine. I\'m too scared to do anything.
        \n“I understand…” he sighs, “Well, it was worth asking anyway.”
        \nJackson pulls me aside.
        \n“Dude, you just… Shut him down. Really hard. If anything I\'d feel like you\'re the one bullying him now.”
        \n“Yeah, but why should we be friends? What if it\'s a trap or something?”
        \n“He genuinely means it.”
        \n“And why should I trust you.”
        \n“Are we friends?”
    </string>

    <string name="yesWeAre">
        “Yes. We\'re friends.”
        \n“Then you trust me.”
        \n“I guess…”
        \n“Then accept his friend request. He means well. Really. I can see it in his eyes.”
        \n“Well… Alright then…”
        \n“Besides, having more friends never hurt anyway. He\'s a nice guy when you get past his tough guy attitude.”
        \n“Alright then…”
        \n“You don\'t seem very sure of yourself.”
        \n“That\'s because I\'m not. No one makes complete changes of personality like that.”
        \n“That\'s just you getting past his tough guy cover. I\'ve been there before.”
        \nHe looks sincere. I turn back to Roman.
        \n“You know what?” I start, “I changed my mind. Let\'s be friends.”
        \nRoman breaks out into a smile.
        \n“Thanks Justin. I hope we\'ll get along…”
        \n“And  also, I accept your apology.”
        \n“Thank you,” he replies, tearing up.
        \n“Oh god. Please don\'t cry.”
        \n“I was yawning.”
        \n“Oh…”
    </string>

    <string name="findingJackson">
        I text Jackson to meet me for lunch. Usually, I like to sit alone in the school cafeteria, but sometimes, we sit together. We eat on a bench in a hallway.
        \n“You know,” says Jackson, “I was thinking of something to get Violet. Like, she deserves it. Actually, I just want to give her something that can last… I don\'t know. Can you think of anything?”
        \n“Cookies?”
        \n“She\'s apparently allergic to the type of oil I use in the cookies, so…”
        \n“That\'s awful… Roman said that your cookies are delicious.”
        \n“Roman..? When did you speak to him?!”
        \n“Um… I was skipping class…”
        \n“Tsk tsk… I thought you were better than that…” he smiles, shaking his head, “Missing a test or something?”
        \n“Um... I was actually trying to avoid someone…”
        \nHis smile fades.
        \n“Who were you trying to avoid?” he asks.
        \n“Ironically… I was trying to avoid Roman.”
        \n“Why would you do that?!”
        \n“Well… I don\'t really want to talk about it. But he said he wanted to meet you after school.”
        \nHe exhales deeply.
        \n“Haven\'t talked to that guy in ages,” he reminisces, “But could you tell me what\'s going on between you two?”

    </string>

    <string name="nothingWrong">
        “No, nothing,” I say.
        \n“Well… You don\'t really seem alright, to be honest. You\'ve been avoiding Roman for some time now, and now you\'re telling me that he\'s the bad guy. Spill the beans, seriously. There\'s something wrong.”
        \n“No there isn\'t!” I exclaim.
        \n“Sorry to be so pushy,” he apologizes, “But I feel like he might be bullying you.”
        \n“Bullying doesn\'t happen in high school,” I reply.
        \n“There you\'re wrong. Bullying happens everywhere. It could be as simple as calling someone a name, but at the end, it\'s all done to hurt someone on purpose. I don\'t know what\'s going on between you and Roman, but I think there\'s something seriously wrong between you and him.”
    </string>

    <string name="notTellHim">
        “Nothing,” I lie, “Nothing\'s going on between us.”
        \n“Liar,” he sniffs.
        \n“Am not.”
        \n“Are too. Come one, are we even friends? I trust you, so why can\'t you trust me? Just tell me. You know me. My mouth is shut when it comes to secrets. And I\'m a one way street. What comes down the street can\'t go back up.”
        \n“Your analogies are weird.”
        \n“I know, but I just want to know what\'s going on. Don\'t worry, I\'m not the one to judge. That\'s not my role. I\'m the supporting friend in your story, and if something\'s going wrong, I\'m going to do my best to help. So what\'s going on?”
    </string>

    <string name="confrontation">
        I meet up with Jackson after school, and we go to the trees in front of school. Sure enough, Roman is there, but his gang of friends aren\'t with him. He recognises me, and I can feel myself shrinking slowly. Jackson keeps me going.
        \n“Hello Banks,” says Roman, tipping an imaginary hat, “And… Jackson?”
        \n“The one and only,” smiles Jackson.
        \nHis smile has no friendliness in it.
        \n“What do you want?” asks Jackson.
        \n“Nothing much really. Now that I look at it, it seems so stupid…” sighs Roman.
        \n“What do you want?!” snaps Jackson.
        \n“Chill… I just want a… I want a cookie…” says Roman.
        \nJackson relaxes immediately, and gives Roman a bag of cookies.
        \n“Thanks dude. I appreciate it,” says Roman, taking a cookie out of the bag.
        \n“How\'s life?” asks Jackson.
        \n“Not the best,” Roman replies.
        \nThey keep small talking, acting like I\'m not there. I can\'t say I mind, but it bugs me a little. I blank out for a while until I realize that Roman and Jackson are looking at me, both expecting an answer.
        \n“Sorry, what?” I ask.
        \n“Roman asked if you\'d forgive him,” explains Jackson.
        \n“I just… Life\'s been rough on me… It\'s my family… And I feel like I\'ve been unleashing all my anger at you. So I\'m sorry for that. Will you forgive me?”
     </string>

    <string name="accepted">
        “Thanks,” I say, taking the bag. I put it in my school bag.
        \nTime for third period… But Roman is there.
    </string>

    <string name="goToClassYC">
        I decide to go to class. Surprisingly, Roman isn\'t here. I guess he decided to skip class. I\'m lucky I didn\'t skip. If I did, I might have had a run-in with him. I put my bag of cookies into my lunch box. Class goes by fast. Lunch time comes around. I go to the cafeteria. I like eating alone. I sit in a far corner and I place my lunch box onto the table.
        \nRoman comes around with his squad, and he picks up my lunch box. He motions to his friends to sit down. He takes a seat in front of me, giving me a mean smile. He opens my lunch box and slowly takes out the contents, one by one, and he lines them all up in a horizontal line in front of me. Finally, he reaches the cookies.
        \n“Where\'d you get this?” he asks.
        \nHe sounds a bit shocked.
        \n“J… Jackson gave it to me,” I whisper.
        \n“Jackson?”
        \n“Yes…”
        \n“You friends with him?”
        \n“I guess…”
        \n“Then today\'s a good day for me. Look kid, get him to meet me after school. Got it?”
        \n“Yes…” I whisper.
        \n“Good boy,” he smiles, and he takes the bag and walks away.
        \nI guess I should find Jackson then… I guess I\'ll go eat lunch with him too. I don\'t want Roman to know where I am.
    </string>

    <string name="goToClassNC">
        I decide to go to class. Surprisingly, Roman isn\'t here. I guess he decided to skip class. I\'m lucky I didn\'t skip. If I did, I might have had a run-in with him. Class goes by fast. Lunch time comes around. I go to the cafeteria. I like eating alone. I sit in a far corner and I place my lunch box onto the table.
        \nRoman comes around with his squad, and he picks up my lunch box. He motions to his friends to sit down. He takes a seat in front of me, giving me a mean smile. He opens my lunch box and slowly takes out the contents, one by one, and he lines them all up in a horizontal line in front of me. He never takes his eyes off of me. I feel like a trapped animal. All I want to do is run as fast as I can. He finds a note from my mom that tells me to enjoy my lunch. He pauses, then he grins eerily.
        \n“What a loser...” he smirks, “Mommy needs to pack little baby\'s lunch.”
        \nI can almost hear a laugh in his voice.
        \n“Well Justin,” he continues, “You\'re in luck. We\'ve got something big going on after school today. And you\'re going to be there. Meet us at the trees in front of school. And if you don\'t come…”
        \nHe lets the threat hang in the air. After a pause, he adds, “See you there.”
        \nHe gets up and leaves me alone.
    </string>

    <string name="notGiveCookie">
        Why would I ever give him a cookie? They\'re mine!
        \n“Sorry, I don\'t have any right now,” I lie.
        \n“Shame. Hey, are you friends with Jackson Baker?”
        \n“Yeah?”
        \n“Could you tell him to come find me after school?”
    </string>

    <string name="doIt">
        “I\'ll do it,” I say.
        \nI don\'t know why I agreed to this, but I probably have to keep up this \‘Andy\' thing up for a while.
        \n“Thanks man, you\'re the best,” he replies.
        \nI can hear the smile in his voice. Are Jackson\'s cookies really that good?! I sort of regret passing up on them.
        \n“Third\'s almost over by the way. Thanks for the talk. And if you tell any of my friends that I\'ve been talking to randos in washrooms, I\'m gonna punch you,” he laughs.
        \nNot sure if he\'s being serious about punching me, but I\'m definitely not going to risk it.
    </string>

    <string name="takeBag">
        I take the bag from him. The cookies seriously smell heavenly.
        \n“Thanks,” I reply, taking a cookie and passing it back to him.
        \nHe takes the bag from me again.
        \n“You know, if you ever see that boy, I want to talk to him. You could go with him if you want. But I want to talk to him again. Haven\'t asked him anything in ages. And his baking just keeps getting better…”
        \n“Sure I guess.”
        \n“Fantastic. See you both then.”
    </string>

    <string name="somethingWrong">
        “Yeah… Something\'s wrong,” I admit.
        \n“Tell me ‘bout it.”
        \n“Well… He bullies me… And by that, I mean he pushes me around, makes fun of me, and… I don\'t know, I just get so scared when he\'s around… I want to run away… Or maybe curl up into a ball and cry…”
        \n“How long has this been going on?”
        \n“Two years?”
        \n“Dude, that\'s serious! Why don\'t you report him to a… I don\'t know, report him to a teacher or someone like that. And why didn\'t you tell me sooner?! I could have helped you…”
        \n“I got scared… Like what if he gets angry and tries to find me when he figures out that I\'m the one that reported him?”
        \n“That\'s ridiculous.”
        \n“But it\'s a valid reason…”
        \n“Not really. If he ever does that, he could go to juvie… Stop over thinking so much.”
        \n“I can\'t help it… I\'m scared.”
        \n“Don\'t worry about it… I\'m here for you, okay? We\'re friends.”
        \n“Thanks I guess… But that doesn\'t change anything…”
        \n“But at least you\'ve got something off your chest.”
        \nI guess I do feel a bit better after telling someone about it.
        \n“Hey Justin… I\'m going to report him. Forget about meeting him, it\'s useless. No one should ever treat my friend like that.”
    </string>

    <string name="tellHim">
        “Well… He bullies me… And by that, I mean he pushes me around, makes fun of me, and… I don\'t know, I just get so scared when he\'s around… I want to run away… Or maybe curl up into a ball and cry…”
        \n“How long has this been going on?”
        \n“Two years?”
        \n“Dude, that\'s serious! Why don\'t you report him to a… I don\'t know, report him to a teacher or someone like that. And why didn\'t you tell me sooner?! I could have helped you…”
        \n“I got scared… Like what if he gets angry and tries to find me when he figures out that I\'m the one that reported him?”
        \n“That\'s ridiculous.”
        \n“But it\'s a valid reason…”
        \n“Not really. If he ever does that, he could go to juvie… Stop over thinking so much.”
        \n“I can\'t help it… I\'m scared.”
        \n“Don\'t worry about it… I\'m here for you, okay? We\'re friends.”
        \n“Thanks I guess… But that doesn\'t change anything…”
        \n“But at least you\'ve got something off your chest.”
        \nI guess I do feel a bit better after telling someone about it.
        \n“Hey Justin… I\'m going to report him. Forget about meeting him, it\'s useless. No one should ever treat my friend like that.”
    </string>

    <string name="confrontRoman">
        “Of course I\'d want to go with you,” I reply, “If he starts acting up, then it\'ll be a two against one.”
        \n“Fighting isn\'t necessary, young grasshopper,” he jokes.
        \n“Sometimes it is,” I object.
        \n“That\'s irrelevant. I\'ll see you after school then. Do you know where he wanted to meet up?”
        \n“Uh… No. But I know where he usually hangs out after school. Mainly because I have to avoid it...”
        \n“Alright then, we\'ll go there”
    </string>

    <string name="forgive">
        “I forgive you,” I reply.
        \nHe looks really relieved.
        \n“Really?”
        \n“Yeah. Just don\'t do it again.”
        \nLame. I should have thought of something better to say.
        \n“I won\'t. I promise.”
        \nRoman looks so happy. Jackson also looks pretty happy. I wonder what they talked about…
        \nAfter that day, Roman didn\'t bother me that much. He nods to me in the hallway sometimes, but other than that, our interactions are kept at a minimum. I\'m glad it\'s all over.

    </string>

    <string name="rejected">
        “No thanks,” I say.
        \nHe seems disappointed.
        \nTime for third period… But Roman is there.
    </string>

    <string name="tellTheTruthYC">
        “It\'s Justin Banks,” I mutter.
        \n“Sorry, what?”
        \n“I\'m Justin. Justin Banks?” I say, louder.
        \n“Justin Banks… Not ringing any bells. Wanna come out? I\'ll recognize you then.”
        \n“Uh…”
    </string>

    <string name="giveCookie">
        “Hang on, I think I have a bag of his cookies on me right now.”
        \nI dig through my bag and take it out, then hold it under the stall door.
        \n“Here you go,” I say, waving the bag around under the door.
        \n“Oh my god, thank you so much,” he says, taking the bag, “Blessed.”
        \nI hear crunching. My stomach rumbles. The crunching pauses for a while.
        \n“Did you want one?” he asks me.
        \nHe holds the bag under the door.
    </string>

    <string name="refuseBag">
        “No thanks,” I say, pushing the bag out from the door, “I just had a bit of gas and yeah…”
        \n“That\'s nasty dude,” replies Roman, taking the bag away.
        \n“We\'re in a washroom.”
        \n“Screw you,” he laughs, “You know, you seem like a cool guy. Are you friends with Jackson?”
        \n“Um… Sure? Yes?”
        \n“If you see him around, I want to talk to him. You could go with him if you want. But I want to talk to him again. Haven\'t asked him anything in ages… And his baking just keeps getting better.”
        \n“Sure... I guess…”
        \n“Great. See you then.”
        \nThe door opens and closes. I guess I should probably go find Jackson…
    </string>

    <string name="notConfrontRoman">
        “I\'d prefer not go to,” I reply.
        \n“Why not?”
        \n“I don\'t want him finding me and yeah…”
        \n“Reasonable. Alright then, I\'ll go alone. Do you know where he wants me to meet him?”
        \n“No… But he usually hangs out by the trees in the front of school.”
        \n“Alright then. I\'ll go there. Bell\'s about to ring. Peace out.”
    </string>

    <string name="aftermath_2">
        After that day, I never saw much of Roman again, except in class. But eventually, he transferred out of that class, and I never really did see him again. I\'ve caught glimpses of someone who looked like him here and there, but nothing more. The bullying has stopped, but I sometimes see Roman\'s friends looking at me and laughing. Even though there\'s a pretty big chance that they\'re not talking about me, there\'s always a slim chance. Jackson never said much about what happened. I\'m just glad it\'s over, for the most part.

    </string>

    <string name="notForgive">
        “I won\'t.”
        \nRoman looks worried.
        \n“Why not?” he asks.
        \n“You\'ve hurt me too much… You know, it\'s super hard to forgive someone right off the bat like this, you know?”
        \n“Yeah… I know exactly how you feel… My mom\'s… I don\'t know, I think he\'s her boyfriend? Well… He bullies me… And to be honest, if he asked me to forgive him, I\'d never do it. It\'s alright though. I understand.”
        \n“Sorry about that.”
        \n“No problem. I\'ll stop bothering you then.”
        \nRoman stayed true to his word. He stopped going after me, and whenever his friends wanted to come over, he\'d stop them. I\'m glad he\'s stopped, and I\'m mostly glad that it\'s over.

    </string>

    <string name="nextDay2">
        The next day, I get called down to the vice principal\'s office during class. I am asked about whether or not I was bullied. I tell them everything. Jackson tells me that he too had been called down and questioned. I don\'t know what happened to Roman, but I didn\'t see him for some time afterwards. There were rumours that he got suspended, then he changed schools. I don\'t know what to believe, but I\'m just glad that it\'s over.

    </string>

    <string name="noWeArent">
        “No. I just like you better than all the other people in class. And we kind of get stuck together in class projects and things like that because no one else wants to work with us,” I frown.
        \n“That\'s harsh man.”
        \n“The truth is harsh.”
        \n“Come talk to me when you\'re in your right mind. I can\'t believe I trusted you. I also don\'t see why you trusted me either. I guess good guys really do finish last.”
        \nI turn back to Roman.
        \n“Sorry about that, but I just realized that I need to go home.”
        \n“It\'s okay,” he replies.
        \nHe looks sad. So does Jackson. I turn around and start walking home. It doesn\'t matter anyway. Nothing matters any more. But at least I\'m probably not going to be bullied...
    </string>
</resources>