<resources>
    <string name="b_b">
        I wake up with a pounding headache.
        Probably got into a fight again last night with my mom\'s boyfriend or lover or whoever she\'s sleeping around with now.
        I\'m sprawled out on the living room floor, still wearing my clothes from yesterday.
        They\'re filthy. I get up and tiptoe to my room. There\'s no one there, thankfully.
        I quickly change my shirt, and don on my leather jacket. The jacket was a gift from my dad before he decided to run away.
        I still can\'t believe he wimped out on us. I check myself in the mirror. I have a barely visible bruise underneath my eye.
        It\'s alright. A wave of pain sends me to my knees. My arm hurts like hell. But I\'ll be alright. I\'ll always be alright.
        I know it\'s a lie, but I\'ll be alright. Guess I should get to school. Home is the last place I want to be.
    </string>

    <string name="atSchoolBBS">
        I take out a cigarette from my pocket. I never really liked smoking, but it helps to ease my nerves.
        My friends join me as they arrive to school.
        \n“Oy Roman, got into a fight yesterday?” laughs Dave.
        \nDave is, more or less, the guy who wants to be like me. He respects me and he\'ll probably do anything
        I ask him to. I\'ve never tested out that theory though. Think I\'ll try it.
        \n“Yeah, want a taste?” I laugh, holding up my fists and throwing a couple of punches in his direction.
        \n“I\'ll take you on,” giggles Vanessa, Dave\'s girlfriend.
        \n“A gentleman is not supposed to hit a lady,” says Matthew, one of my friends.
        \n“She\'s a b*tch, not a lady,” I joke.
        \nVanessa tries to shove me down. She\'s too weak. Dave and Matthew laugh at her futile attempt.
        \n“We should probably get into school,” I say, looking at my watch.
        \n“What\'s the big deal? We still got time,” says Dave.
        \n“I want to see if I can see that guy,” I reply, “I got something for him.”
        \n“What\'re you thinking?” asks Matthew.
        \n“I got some… Tape in my bag,” I grin, digging into my bag and producing a roll of duct tape.
        \n“Damn Roman. You gonna tie him up?” laughs Vanessa.
        \n“Awh, I don\'t even know if he\'s gonna be there. But if he\'s here, he\'s gonna pass by the art hallway.”
    </string>

    <string name= "artHallBBS">
        We sit down on the stairs, in perfect formation. We\'re sitting so that the only place where he can walk is in between us.
        My other friends had joined me. Vanessa went back to join her friends. We wait silently, like wolves, waiting for the boy.
        \nI dig around in my bag, and find an old utility bill. Why the hell did my mom leave this in my bag… It\'s useless anyway.
        My mom doesn\'t have a job. She just hooks up with random guys, and they pay our bills. I ball up the bill in anger.
        \nFinally, I see the boy approaching, his head down, trying not to make eye contact with me.
    </string>

    <string name="boyInfoBBS">
        I stare at him. He\'s a pretty scrawny kid. Sort of ugly, too. I felt superior to him the minute I met him.
        He was the perfect victim. I knew I had to act stronger than everyone else. I just knew it. The only way to
        keep my friends\' respect was to be the strong one. I didn\'t want to show them the sniveling little kid that I was.
        I wanted them to see someone they could look up to.
        I could easily beat him up if I really wanted to. But that\'s a treat for another day.
        I notice him staring back at me.
        \n“What\'re you looking at,” I sneer.
    </string>

    <string name="throwPaperBBS">
        I throw the paper ball at him, and it hits his head. A perfect headshot. My friends laugh. I smile.
        I didn\'t think I\'d hit him in the head, but I did, and I\'m proud of myself.
        \n“Pick it up,” I laugh.
    </string>

    <string name="pickUpBallBBS">
        “Now give it here,” I smile.
    </string>

    <string name="giveMeBallBBS">
        He puts the ball into my hand.
        \n“Stand there,” I order, pointing at a tile in front of me.
        \nHe stands in front of me, waiting for me to say something, to do something. He looks down, but I catch him taking occasional peeks at me. I dig into my bag and find the roll of duct tape. Perfect. Everything is going according to plan.
        \n“Don\'t move,” I order him.
        \nI turn to Dave. Guess now\'s a good time to test out my theory.
        \n“Tape him up real good, will ya? Just unroll all of it and make sure he can\'t move his arms,” I whisper to him, handing him the roll of tape.
        \nDave smiles and takes the roll of tape from me. He slaps a piece of tape onto the boy\'s mouth. That was a smart move. The last thing I\'d need is a snivelling little kid. He unravels the tape around the boy\'s arms and bag. I watch him slowly become a tape mummy.
        \n“Come here,” I tell the boy.
        \nHe shuffles towards me, and I smile. He looks funny. I pull out a paint marker from my bag.
        \n“S… T… U… P… I… D…” I mutter.
        \nI look back at the word written across his arms. Not bad. I shove him onto the floor. He starts wiggling around like a fish. I laugh, and I kick him. Stop. moving. My friends follow my actions. One kick per person. I start to feel a little bit bad for him.
        \n“Take the tape off, the kid needs to get to class,” I tell my friends, then turning to the boy, I say, “See you at lunch.”
        \nI walk away. My friends can handle the situation pretty well. Guess I should get going to class…
    </string>

    <string name="heWalksAwayBBS">
        “Hey, hey, did you not hear me?”
        \nI get up. I feel angered. He starts running away in the opposite direction
        \n“Run you dumb turtle,” I shout, annoyed, “I\'ll see you at lunch.”
        \nI sit back down.
        \n“Mother f*cker,” I mutter.
        \n“Calm down Rome,” says Matthew, “Take a chill pill.”
        \n“I\'m just feeling a bit pissed, man,” I sigh.
        \n“Just take it easy, okay?”
        \n“I think we\'d better get to class.”
        \n“I\'m skipping.”
        \n“Oh. Well, I need to get to class. Got a… A project thing due for tomorrow, so I need to work on it,” I lie.
        \n“Sure you do,” he smiles.
        \n“B*tch,” I laugh, “I just want an education, you idiot.”
        \n“You\'ve got me there nerd,” he laughs.
        \n“I hate you,” I laugh, shoving him.
        \n“Sure you do. Get to class you nerd, or you gonna be late.”
    </string>

    <string name="firstPeriodBBS">
        First period is fine. The teacher is chill, and I can literally put my feet up on the desk and no one will care. None of my friends are in this class, so I try to work when I can to make up for my other grades. This class is pretty easy, so I think I\'ve got this. Before I know it, the bell rings, and I leave to go to my next class
    </string>

    <string name="heWalkedAwayBBS">
        He turns around.
        \n“Hey, pick it up,” I sneer.
        \nHe stops in his tracks and picks it up.
        \n“Now give it here,” I smile.
    </string>

    <string name="travelTimeBBS">
        The hallways are pretty packed when I get out. As I round a corner, a little kid runs into me. I push him away, and I recognize it as the kid.
        \n“What do you want, punk,” I sneer.
        \nI\'m a bit annoyed, since he\'s going to make me late. I\'m already trying to keep up a good attendance record, but if people keep running into me, there\'s going to be a problem.
    </string>

    <string name="heSaysNothingBBS">
        “N… Nothing,” he stammers.
        \n“Oh really? Then you don\'t mind if I do this?”
        \nI shove him against a locker and walk away. He deserved it for blocking my way. I hope I\'m not late.
    </string>

    <string name="heStaresAtMeBBS">
        He doesn\'t do anything. He stands there in front of me, and he stares.
        \n“What do you want?” I say.
        \nI can\'t believe he\'s wasting my time by just staring at me.
        \n“What you staring at? Get away from me, loser,” I snap.
        \nI walk away from him. What a weirdo.
    </string>

    <string name="heTurnsAroundBBS">
        He sprints the opposite direction of me. What a weirdo. He could have at least apologized. I should get to class.
    </string>

    <string name="secondPeriodBBS">
        I arrive to class on time, surprisingly. Dave and Vanessa are already there. I sit behind them, thanks to alphabetical order. We\'re in the back of the class, but I\'ve been asked a few times to move to the front. I declined every time, which earned me a trip to the vice president\'s office every other day.
        “Good morning class,” says my teacher, “Today we\'ll be learning about…”
        I put my earbuds into my ears and drown her endless droning with my music. I don\'t care much for this class. I\'m not going to measure triangles in my life any time soon. I close my eyes and let the music take me into a different realm.
        Dave wakes me up. I fell asleep. My music is still blasting in my ears. I had a great nap.
    </string>

    <string name="endOfDay1BBS">
        I go outside to my usual hangout spot, at the trees in front of school. Dave, Vanessa, and Matthew are there. We talk about the usual stuff, and Vanessa shoves me as usual, and everything goes on as it\'s supposed to go. I see the boy across the street. I ignore him. I should be going home too, or else my mom\'s going to get worried.
    </string>

    <string name="homeBBS">
        I arrive home. My mom is cooking.
        \n“Mom, I\'m home,” I say half-heartedly.
        \n“Dinner will be ready soon, love,” she says.
        \n“Mom, it\'s only three in the afternoon.”
        \n“Is Thanos home?” asks an unfamiliar voice.
        \nI guess it\'s one of her boyfriends. I think she mentioned someone named Larry… But I don\'t care. I\'m not in the mood for a fight or anything.
        \n“Yes dear,” says my mom.
        \n“Tell him to get his stupid a** out of here, Jennifer.”
        \n“But sweetheart-”
        \n“Do you really want to argue with me, Jennifer? I pay for everything in this house. Electricity, water, heat… If you want to argue with me, I will say goodbye, and you\'ll never see me again. The bills won\'t pay themselves.”
    </string>

    <string name="stayHomeBBS">
        “No,” I say, “No way. This is my house, and that\'s my mom. No one, and I repeat, no one is allowed to speak to my mom like that. B*stard.”
        \n“Roman,” says my mom, “I think it\'s best if you-”
        \n“Little punk. What did you say about me?”
        \n“I said you were a b*stard. Do you want more words? Total c*nt, a f*cking r*tard, a-”
        \n“Roman! Watch your mouth!” snaps my mom.
        \n“At least I\'m not talking about you,” I snap.
        \nShe gets a pained look in her face, and she turns back to her cooking. Larry addresses me.
        \n“Roman. I\'m going to give you until the count of three. If in three seconds you\'re not gone…”
        \nHe lets the threat hang in the air.
        \n“Larry,” I reply, “I am so sorry, but with your intelligence, you\'d barely make it past one.”
        \nI can see the anger in his eyes. I smile cockily. Let him come to me. Let him make the first swing. It\'s called self defense for a reason. He raises his hand. I brace myself to take the hit. To my surprise, my mom holds his hand back when he tries to hit me.
        \n“Larry…” she says, “Please don\'t…”
        \n“It\'s him or me, Jenn.”
        \nShe takes a deep breath. She raises her head. I can see the determination in her eyes.
        \n“I choose my son, Larry,” she replies.
        \nLarry\'s face turns purple in a matter of seconds. It\'s hilarious seeing his face transition into all those shades, but I keep my face blank. I can tell that he can see my mom\'s determination too, since he puts his hand down, and faces her instead.
        \n“Fine,” he relents, “I\'m leaving. Goodbye, Jennifer. I hope you and your son go rot in hell.”
        \n“We\'ll see you there,” she snarls, “Now get out.”
        \nShe\'s got serious mode on. I got to admit, I really admire my mom when she\'s got serious mode on. Larry packs up his belongings in his car, then drives away. I\'m glad he\'s done. I\'m completely drained. I go upstairs and go to sleep.
    </string>

    <string name="day2BBS">
        Larry is back when I wake up. Apparently, he had begged his way back into my mom\'s heart. He\'s the worst.
        \nI arrive to school early, and find my friends. Matthew\'s eyeing Vanessa a lot more than usual, and Dave is trying to take up all the attention.
        \n“I heard Larry got kicked out yesterday,” says Matthew.
        \nHis parents usually let me crash on their couch whenever my home situation gets too hectic, so him knowing about my personal life isn\'t that surprising.
        \n“Yeah well, he came back,” I snap.
        \n“Chill out Roman, I\'m sure everything\'s gonna turn out alright eventually,” he replies.
        \n“He\'s so gonna get it today,” I snarl, “Sometimes, I want to punch that guy in the face so hard that he gets knocked out for days…”
        \n“Don\'t worry,” says Vanessa, putting a reassuring hand on my shoulder, “I\'m sure your mom will find the guts to kick him out again for good.”
        \nThe bell rings, and we go in different directions. First and second period go by quick.
    </string>

    <string name="iSkippedThirdPeriodBBS">
        I couldn\'t help myself. I needed a smoke really badly, since I had been feeling agitated the entire day. Larry just p*sses me off. More than I can handle. I go into a washroom in the shadier part of school. Usually, no one goes there anyway, so a quick smoke won\'t bother anyone. I enter the washroom and light my cigarette. I take a drag. Damn that feels good. Then I notice a closed stall. I knock to make sure no one\'s there.
    </string>

    <string name="someoneAnsweredBBS">
        “Yes?” squeaks a high pitched voice.
        \n“Oh sorry, didn\'t think anyone was here.”
        \n“It\'s okay,” replies the voice.
        \nIt\'s now a much higher pitched voice. I hope it\'s not someone I know. I guess I should check to make sure.
        \n“Say, who are you?” I ask, “I\'m Roman Thanos.”
    </string>

    <string name="heSaidHeWasAndyBBS">
        “My name\'s Andy…” he says.
        \nHe seems hesitant. Which is understandable, since not many people randomly strike up conversations with people is washrooms.
        \n“Well… You wanna come out? You skipping too? Or you taking a dump. Because then I\'m not gonna bother you.”
        \n“Uh… I\'m uh… Just here.”
        \n“Skipping then. Want a smoke?”
        \nI guess I\'ll take a friendly approach to him.
        \n“You\'re not supposed to smoke in school…”
        \n“Screw it. My life, my rules.”
        \n“Why\'re you like this?”
        \n“Messed up family, messed up friends, messed up me,” I chuckle, “Just saying, I don\'t usually talk with strangers in bathroom stalls. If you wondered.”
        \n“Ah… No, I didn\'t... “
        \n“Well… Life\'s been sh*tty. Like this washroom. Ha, ha… Get it? No? Okay…”
        \n“Uh I got it. But it was a really bad joke. Sorry.”
        \n“Say… You sound really familiar. You remind me of one of the kids from middle school. That kid was a crazy good baker man... I can\'t really put my finger on him right now, but he goes to our school.“
        \n“Wait, do you mean Jackson Baker?!”
        \n“I think so, yeah. I remember his last name. I\'d kill for one of his cookies right now.”
    </string>

    <string name="heApologizedBBS">
        “Sorry man, I don\'t have any,” he says.
        \n“Hey, are you friends with Baker?”
        \n“Yeah...”
        \n“Can you get him to come meet me after school?”
    </string>

    <string name="heSaidHeWouldntDoItBBS">
        “I\'m sorry, but I\'m not going to do that for someone I just met. And we met under very strange circumstances too…” he says.
        \n“True that. Well it was nice talking, Andy. If you ever change your mind, tell him to find me in front of the school near the trees.”
        \nI leave the washroom. I wonder if I\'ll see him… I guess I\'ll wait after school for him. If he doesn\'t come… Oh well.
    </string>

    <string name="heSaidHeWouldDoItBBS">
        “I\'ll do it,” he says.
        \n“Thanks man, you\'re the best,” I smile.
        \nI really can\'t wait. It\'s been such a long time since I\'ve talked to Jackson. And he makes amazing cookies.
        \n“Third\'s almost over by the way,” I tell him, “Thanks for the talk. And if you tell any of my friends that I\'ve been talking to randos in washrooms, I\'m gonna punch you.”
        \nI laugh and leave the washroom. I hope everything goes well.
    </string>

    <string name="heHadABagOfCookiesBBS">
        “Hang on, I think I have a bag of his cookies on me right now,” says Andy.
        \nI hear some rummaging behind the door, and a hand holds a bag underneath the door.
        \n“Here you go,” he says, waving the bag around under the door.
        \n“Oh my god, thank you so much,” I say, taking the bag, “Blessed.”
        \nI eat the cookie. They\'re as good as I remember them. Crunchy on the outside, soft and melty on the inside. I hear rumbling underneath the door. I stop.
        \n“Did you want one?” I ask him.
        \nI hold the bag under the door. After all, they\'re not my cookies.
    </string>

    <string name="heTookTheBagBBS">
        He takes the bag from me and I hear some ruffling noises.
        \n“Thanks,” he replies, passing the bag back to him.
        \nI takes the bag from him.
        \n“You know, if you ever see that boy, I want to talk to him. You could go with him if you want. But I want to talk to him again. Haven\'t asked him anything in ages. And his baking just keeps getting better…” I say.
        \n“Sure I guess.”
        \n“Fantastic. See you both then.”
    </string>

    <string name="heDidntTakeTheBagBBS">
        “No thanks,” he says, pushing the bag out from the door, “I just had a bit of gas and yeah…”
        \n“That\'s nasty dude,” I reply, taking the bag away.
        \n“We\'re in a washroom.”
        \n“Screw you,” I laugh, “You know, you seem like a cool guy. Are you friends with Jackson?”
        \n“Um… Sure? Yes?”
        \n“If you see him around, I want to talk to him. You could go with him if you want. But I want to talk to him again. Haven\'t asked him anything in ages… And his baking just keeps getting better.”
        \n“Sure... I guess…”
        \n“Great. See you then.”
        \nI leave the washroom. I\'m glad I get to see him again. And I can\'t wait go get more cookies.
    </string>

    <string name="waitingOutsideSchoolBBS">
        I wait outside at the trees after school. Dave, Vanessa, and Matthew have gone to the park. When we\'re not here, we usually hang out there.
    </string>

    <string name="jacksonAndTheBoyCameBBS">
        I recognize the boy and Jackson.
        \n“Hello,” I say, tipping an imaginary hat, “And… Jackson?”
        \n“The one and only,” smiles Jackson.
        \nHis smile has no friendliness in it.
        \n“What do you want?” asks Jackson.
        \n“Nothing much really. Now that I look at it, it seems so stupid…” I sigh.
        \n“What do you want?!” snaps Jackson.
        \n“Chill… I just want a… I want a cookie…” I reply.
        \nJackson relaxes immediately, and gives me a bag of cookies.
        \n“Thanks dude. I appreciate it,” I say, taking a cookie out of the bag.
        \n“How\'s life?” asks Jackson.
        \n“Not the best,” I reply.
        \n“How so?”
        \n“Well… I have family problems.”
        \n“Dang… I\'m sorry. What kind of problems”
        \n“You\'re treading in dangerous waters.”
        \n“It doesn\'t matter. You\'re there, and I want to drag you out.”
        \n“Thanks, I guess,” I smile, “It\'s just that I get so angry.”
        \n“That sucks. Need help with anything?”
        \n“Nah, it\'s okay. Matthew\'s got my back.”
        \n“One of your friends, right?”
        \n“Yeah. He\'s a real bro.”
        \n“I\'m glad. You know what I think you should do?”
        \n“What?”
        \n“Apologize to Justin. He told me that you\'ve been making fun of him. And he feels unhappy about it. You\'re literally the source of all his problems. Sorry for being so direct. He can\'t really hear us right now.”
        \nI look at the boy. He\'s staring blankly ahead. I feel sort of bad. He\'s just a person, like anyone else.
        \n“I guess I could. Will you forgive me, Justin?”
        \n“Sorry, what?” asks Justin, shaking his head.
        \n“Roman asked if you\'d forgive him,” explains Jackson.
        \n“I just… Life\'s been rough on me… It\'s my family… And I feel like I\'ve been unleashing all my anger at you. So I\'m sorry for that. Will you forgive me?”
    </string>

    <string name="heForgivesMeBBS">
        “I forgive you,” he replies.
        \nI feel so relieved.
        \n“Really?” I ask.
        \n“Yeah. Just don\'t do it again.”
        \n“I won\'t. I promise.”
        \nI\'m so happy. Jackson also looks pretty happy. Justin\'s looking at us with a confused expression.
        After that day, I didn\'t bother him much. I still nod to him in the hallway sometimes, but other than that, our interactions are kept at a minimum. I hope Justin feels better now.
        \n“Yeah. Just don\'t do it again.”
        \n“I won\'t. I promise.”
        \nI\'m so happy. Jackson also looks pretty happy. Justin\'s looking at us with a confused expression.
        After that day, I didn\'t bother him much. I still nod to him in the hallway sometimes, but other than that, our interactions are kept at a minimum. I hope Justin feels better now.
    </string>

    <string name="heDoesNotForgiveMeBBS">
        “I won\'t,” he says.
        \n“Why not?” I ask.
        \n“You\'ve hurt me too much… You know, it\'s super hard to forgive someone right off the bat like this, you know?”
        \nI\'m starting to feel really bad. But at least I understand.
        \n“Yeah… I know exactly how you feel… My mom\'s… I don\'t know, I think he\'s her boyfriend? Well… He bullies me… And to be honest, if he asked me to forgive him, I\'d never do it. It\'s alright though. I understand.”
        \n“Sorry about that.”
        \n“No problem. I\'ll stop bothering you then.”
        \nI stopped bothering him. Even when Dave and the others wanted to go at him, I\'d stop them. I made it clear that Justin was on our no go list. Life didn\'t really change much then, but at least Justin has one less problem to think of.
    </string>

    <string name="jacksonCameBBS">
        Jackson walked out, waving at me when he saw me. I smiled and waved back. After all this time, he\'s still his friendly self.
        \n“Hey Rome,” he says, giving me the Vulcan salute.
        \n“Jackie my boy,” I grin, returning the salute.
        \n“I heard you wanted to talk to me or something.”
        \n“Yeah, I was wondering if you had any more of your legendary cookies?”
        \n“Sorry, I gave my last pack out today,” he replies.
        \nI\'m disappointed.
        \n“Oh… Alright then,” I frown.
        \n“Cheer up Rome. Look, I have something I want to talk to you about. You know Justin?”
        \n“Who\'s Justin?”
        \n“Justin is my friend. He told me everything. You push him around, call him names, beat him up… What is wrong with you?! You were such a good guy back then. What happened?”
        \n“Look man, forget about me, but where did that come from?!”
        \n“Stop playing dumb. You aren\'t the Roman I know.”
        \nWait… Justin… Is that the boy\'s name?
        \n“Wait. I think I know who you\'re talking about.”
        \n“Yeah. All I want to know is why.”
        \n“Life\'s been rough,” I explain, “And I\'ve changed. I\'m not who I used to be. I\'m better.”
        \n“You\'re wrong. You\'re worse. You used to be such a nice guy. And a bit of a nerd, too. What happened?”
        \n“It\'s none of your business,” I snap.
        \n“Yes it is,” he replies, “Since you\'re being a bully. I don\'t care if you go on doing whatever you do, it\'s just that I don\'t want you to hurt Justin any more than you\'ve already hurt him. He\'s broken. And it\'s all. Your. Fault.”
        \nI\'m taken aback.
        \n“So what? It doesn\'t affect me…” I stammer.
        \n“And if he kills yourself, it\'ll be your fault.”
        \n“But it\'s his choice. Not mine.”
        \n“That\'s where you\'re wrong. It\'s your choice. It was always your choice. You choose to make him feel worthless, you choose to make him feel like he\'s better off dead. Why do you do this?”
        \n“I… I don\'t know,” I admit.
        \n“So you do it without reason? Geez man, I thought you were better than this.”
        \n“I\'m sorry.”
        \n“Don\'t say that to me, say that to my friend.”
        \n“I… He won\'t forgive me. I know it.”
        \nHe stares at me with a burning hatred in his eyes.
        \n“I won\'t bother him again, okay? I swear I won\'t do it.”
        \nThe hatred doesn\'t waver when he smiles.
        \n“Good. I\'ll bring you a pack of cookies tomorrow,” he smiles.
        \nI kept my promise and never bothered him again.
    </string>

    <string name="noOneCameBBS">
        I waited and I waited. No one came. I guess the guy just forgot about me. I go home.
    </string>

    <string name="day3BBS">
        The next day, I was called down to the vice principal\'s office. They asked me questions about this boy named Justin. I didn\'t admit anything. Why should I?
        Turns out Jackson had snaked me. I was suspended. Later, my mom decided that it was best to move, since she had found a new boyfriend in a different town. I changed schools, and I never really kept contact with anyone else. I guess it\'s for the best.
    </string>

    <string name="heSaidHeWasJustinBBS">
        The voice mutters something I can\'t really here.
        \n“Sorry, what?” I frown.
        \n“I\'m Justin. Justin Banks?” says the voice, louder.
        \n“Justin Banks… Not ringing any bells. Wanna come out? I\'ll recognize you then.”
        \n“Uh…”
    </string>

    <string name="noOneCameOutBBS">
        “I\'m just going to stay in here,” he replies.
        \n“You\'re a weird kid, aren\'t you,” I snickers.
        \n“What do you mean?”
        \nThe voice is deeper. I think I can recognize it now...
        \n“Wait. You\'re not a weird kid, you\'re the weird kid!” I exclaim.
        \n“What?”
        \n“You\'re the kid!”
        \n“How do you know?”
        \nBy now, I\'m sure it\'s that idiot from third period.
        \n“Oh boy… Wait till the others hear about this!” I smirk, “Well Justin, you\'re in luck. We\'ve got something big going on after school today. And you\'re going to be there. Meet us at the trees in front of school. And if you don\'t come…”
        \nI pause for effect. Drama is key when it comes to this kid.
        \n“See you there,” I smile.
        \nI throw my cigarette into the trash can and leave the washroom. I\'m still agitated as f*ck. I kick a locker, leaving a sizable dent in it.
        \n“He\'s so gonna get it today,” I whisper, a smile on my face.
    </string>

    <string name="someoneCameOutBBS">
        Someone walks out of the stall. It\'s the boy.
        \n“Hey, it\'s you,” I say stupidly.
        \n“It\'s me…” he mutters.
        \n“Thought you were too much of a goody two-shoes to skip anything,” I smirk.
        \nHe looks down at his shoes.
        \n“Looks like I was wrong,” I continues, “Maybe you can help me with something after school. Come find me and the others at the trees in front of school. And if you don\'t come...”
        \nI let the threat hang in the air for a while for dramatic effects. Then I turn to the door.
        \n“See you, Banks,” I smile, and I leaves the washrooms.
    </string>

    <string name="noOneAnsweredBBS">
        No one answered, which is good. I manage to open the stall door just to make sure. I put a door stop at the door to make sure no one can enter. By the time the bell had rung, the washroom had a very hazy smoke scent.
    </string>

    <string name="lunchBBS">
        I find my friends in the school cafeteria. I like lunch. Food is great. Unfortunately, I forgot to bring food with me. I spot the boy from yesterday sitting alone. I smile. I guess I can get something from him. I go to him and pick up his lunch box. I motion to my friends to sit down at a different table. They smile and laugh and do whatever they usually do. I take a seat in front of the boy, giving him a smile. I open his lunch box and slowly take out the contents, one by one, and lining them all up in a horizontal line in front of him.
    </string>

    <string name="iSawANoteBBS">
        I find a cheesy note from his mom that tells him to enjoy his lunch. I sort of want my mom to do this for me, but I know for a fact that she\'d never do this for me. I grin.
        \n“What a loser...” I smirk, “Mommy needs to pack little baby\'s lunch. Well Justin,” I continue, taking his name from the note, “You\'re in luck. We\'ve got something big going on after school today. And you\'re going to be there. Meet us at the trees in front of school. And if you don\'t come…”
        \nI let the threat hang in the air. After a pause, I add, “See you there.”
        \nI get up and rejoin my friends. They\'re talking animatedly about irrelevant things.
        \n“Hey guys,” I say, “I have a bit of a something planned for tomorrow.”
        \n“What is it?” asks Dave.
        \n“We\'re going to have a bit of… Fun… With that boy over there,” I say, nodding to the boy.
        \nTo my surprise, he\'s disappeared. I laugh.
        \n“With Justin, sorry,” I laugh, “I swear he was right there…”
        \nVanessa looks a bit worried. Doesn\'t matter. She\'s got a good family, a good home, a good boyfriend… If she wants to be a complete p*ssy, she has all the right to do so.
    </string>

    <string name="afterSchool2BBS">
        I wait at the trees in front of the school with my friends. Justin arrives a while later, right after the bell. What a good kid. I smile and wave at him when I see him approaching.
        \n“And here is our special guest, Mr. Justin Banks!” I proclaim.
        \nMy friends all laugh and applaud. Vanessa looks concerned. What a p*ssy.
        \n“Are you sure we should do this?” she asks.
        \n“Are you chicken?” I ask, not wanting to offend the feminist side of her.
        \n“No, but I really don\'t think-”
        \n“Look Vanessa, if you don\'t want to go with the plan, then just get outta here. No one wants you anyway, except this piece of trash,” I laugh, pushing Dave.
        \n“He\'s more of a man than you\'ll ever be,” says Vanessa, her voice developing a frigid tone, “Come on, Dave.”
        \n“But Vanessa…” he protests.
        \n“Fine! Be that way! Ugh!” she replies, and she walks away.
        \nMatthew follows her away. I feel like he really likes her.
        \n“Dave… Why do you even date that girl…” I groan.
        \n“She\'s a one of a kind beauty,” replies Dave.
        \nI roll my eyes. Then I grab Justin\'s backpack roughly and drag him further away into the school parking lot. Everyone knows that the parking lot doesn\'t have security cameras monitoring it, since our school is too poor to afford a decent security system. And I\'m going to take advantage of it.
        \n“We\'re going to have some fun, Justin. It\'s a shame that those two had to leave…” I grin.
        \nI push him roughly and he falls flat on the asphalt. I feel powerful again.
        \n“Get up,” I urge.
        \n“Get up,” echoes Dave.
        \nHe gets back on his feet, and Dave throws him down. I laugh. He tells him to get up, only to push him down again. We take turns. I finally feel like I have control of some aspect of my life. It might be small and insignificant, but I am in control. We start kicking and punching him. He\'s cowering underneath our hits. I smile, imagining that he\'s Larry. I kick him hard.“Hey!” shouts a voice.
        \nDave and I stop kicking Justin. A teacher comes out and runs out to Justin. He\'s not moving. The teacher starts checking his vital signs.
        \n“Oh shoot…” I mutter.
        \n“Did we kill him?!” whispers Dave.
        \n“He\'s still breathing,” I whisper back.
    </string>

    <string name="nextBBS">
        Needless to say, Dave and I were sent back home. A bunch of questioning and talks and legal issues later, we were expelled. I guess I kind of gave up then. I broke contact with all my friends, ran away from home a few times, and started living life the way I wanted to. I don\'t mind beating up people now and then. I get in trouble more than I should. Call me aggressive, but I\'m just doing what I can to survive in this f*cked up world.
    </string>

    <string name="iSawCookiesBBS">
        I reach for the cookies. They look oddly familiar… Like a forgotten childhood memory.
        \n“Where\'d you get this?” I ask.
        \n“J… Jackson gave it to me,” he whispers.
        \n“Jackson?”
        \n“Yes…”
        \nI remember Jackson. He used to go to middle school with me. I remember he used to bake cookies for the kids from school.
        \n“You friends with him?” I ask.
        \n“I guess…”
        \n“Then today\'s a good day for me. Look kid, get him to meet me after school. Got it?”
        \n“Yes…” he whispers.
        \n“Good boy,” I smile, and I take the bag and walk back to my friends. Guess I\'ll be meeting Jackson after school...
    </string>

    <string name="agreeToLeaveBBS">
        “Fine, I\'ll go,” I reply, “I\'ll go crash at a friend\'s house. Bye mom.”
        \nI leave my house and go to Matthew\'s house. His parents understand my situation, so I\'m welcome any time.
    </string>

    <string name="nextDayBBS">
        I go to school later than usual. I had to creep into my house to get a change of clothes. I go inside to find my friends. I see Dave with the boy. He seems to be… It reminds me of Larry and my mom. Dave was trying to
    </string>

    <string name="stealHisBagBBS">
        I should probably do something about this. I walk towards them.
        \n“Hey Dave,” I say as casually as possible, “What\'re you doing?”
        \n“Just trying to play with this kid,” he replies, “He\'s looking for you by the way.”
        \n“What do you want?” I ask.
        \n“I have something from Jen-”
        \n“Hey Dave, can you leave us alone for a bit?” I ask.
        \n“Sure, anything,” he replies.
        \nHe pushes past the boy and leaves.
        \n“How do you have something from my mom?” I ask incredulously.
        \n“I uh… Went to your house yesterday. And she gave me this note…”
        \nHe gives me a folded piece of paper.
        \n“Did you read it?” I ask.
        \n“No. I figured that it was personal or something so…”
        \n“And going to my house is definitely not personal.”
        \n“Sorry…”
        \n“How do you even know where I live anyway.?”
        \n“You threw a paper with your address on it at me…”
        \n“Oh… Sorry about that.”
        \nI sort of regret doing that. But deep inside, I\'m a bit relieved...
        \n“Your family situation sucks.”
        \n“You met Larry, didn\'t you.”
        \n“He like, bullies your mom… He\'s scary.”
        \n“You haven\'t seen him drunk yet. That\'s when the demon is unleashed from hell.”
        \n“I… Wow, that must be awful…”
        \nIf only he knew. You know… I think we could get along.
        \n“Yeah man. Geez… I want to talk more and stuff but… Bell\'s about to ring. And you\'re a goody two shoes. Can\'t have you be late. So… Talk to you later, maybe… Or actually, do you want to meet up somewhere? I just… Need to get something off my chest.”
        \n“Uh… Okay?”
        \n“4:00 pm, Rollingston Park. I\'m going alone, since my friends are… They\'re just a bit weird, and I don\'t think they\'d want to talk about my situation. Like, they all have their own problems and stuff, so I\'d rather not bother them.”
        \n“Um…”
        \n“Wait, do I scare you?”
        \n“Uh…”
        \n“I probably do… You can bring your friends if you want. I don\'t mind. But get the friends you trust because I don\'t want to be sweeping up your loose ends.”
        \n“Uh… Okay…”
        \n“See you then. Get to class. You\'re going to be late if you don\'t.”
    </string>

    <string name="stealANoteBBS">
        “Dave! Quit it!” I exclaim.
        \nDave stops and they both turn to see me.
        \n“But—” Dave protests.
        \n“I\'m the only one who should be shoving this squeaker around, not you. Got it?”
        \n“Yeah yeah… But he\'s got a note, Rome! I think you should read it,” he smiles, handing over the note to me, “Bet it\'s a cheesy love letter to some useless girl.”
        \nI open up the note and read it.
        \nRoman, I\'m going to kick Larry out of the house. I\'ve had enough of him and his mean and hurtful words. I\'m sorry you had to see him be mean to you. I hope you\'re doing alright. Come back home… Love, Mom.
        \nMy eyes narrow. I doubt she has the strength to go against him. She\'s pretty weak willed.
        \n“Where did you get this?” I ask.
        \n“I went to your h—”
        \n“Dave get out of here, I want to talk to this kid one on one,” I interrupt, throwing a mean look to Dave.
        \nDave nods, scared, and he walks away, cursing and muttering under his breath.
        \n“So you went to my house,” I say.
        \n“Yeah, and—”
        \n“And my mother gave this to you.”
        \n“Not really, she actually threw it out—”
        \n“So she threw it out the window. That\'s all I am to her. Just another thing that can get thrown out a window.”
        \n“Will you please just listen?!” he snaps.
        \nHe immediately gets a scared puppy dog look.
        \n“I\'m sorry,” he whispers.
        \n“No, no… Don\'t be… I shouldn\'t have been like that. Let\'s start from the beginning. Why did you go to my house? And how do you even know where I live? Creepy stalker.”
        \n“Uh… You know that paper you threw at me yesterday…”
        \n“Old utility bill. Right.”
        \n“Well I decided to check the place out, and uh... Larry yelled at me for going to your house, and then Jennifer came outside and bought Larry back in and then she wrote it and threw it outside so I picked it up.”
        \n“You read it, didn\'t you.”
    </string>

    <string name="heSaidHeDidntReadItBBS">
        “Liar. Then how did you know to give it to me?” I ask.
        \n“I\'m sorry! I just didn\'t want you to be mad at me… I\'m sorry...”
        \n“Man… Am I really that screwed up...”
        \n“It\'s just that… I was curious...”
        \n“Curiosity killed the cat,” he remarks dryly.
        \n“I\'m sorry,” I reply, ashamed at my lie.
        \n“Look man, let\'s meet up sometime tonight. I guess I just need someone to talk to.”
        \n“Um… Well...”
        \n“Still don\'t trust me? Bring someone with you if you want. I\'ll understand.”
        \n“I have a curfew at seven...”
        \n“Fine. Four in the afternoon on the school roof. Know how to get there?”
        \n“That\'s dangerous.”
        \n“Fine. You know Rollingston Park? It\'s right near here.”
        \n“I\'ll search it up.”
        \n“Cool, see you then.”
        \nThe bell rings and he leaves. Time to go to class.
    </string>

    <string name="heSaidHeReadItBBS">
        “Well… Dang. Do you want to meet up sometime tonight? I don\'t know… I guess I just need someone to talk to,” I sigh.
        \n“Um… I… Uh…”
        \nHe\'s probably thinking that I\'m acting really weird. Not everyone gets sudden change of heart. But once you see yourself becoming the guy you hate the most… I\'d want to change.
        \n“Bring someone with you if you want. I understand. I probably terrify you,” I reason.
        \n“Uh… But I need to be home by seven.”
        \n“‘Kay. Four in the afternoon?”
        \n“Um… Sure…”
        \n“Alright. I\'ll be on the roof of the Glass Piazza. You know how to get there?”
        \n“That\'s dangerous.”
        \n“Fine, then the park. Rollingston Park. It\'s right near here.”
        \n“Uh… I\'ll search it up.”
        \n“Cool, see you there then.”
        \nThe bell rings and I leave. I can\'t wait to talk to the boy… But I\'m a bit scared too.
    </string>

    <string name="afterSchoolBBS">
        After school, I walk to the park. I used to come here a lot. I sit on a swing, and put my earphones on. It feels sort of nostalgic. I see the boy come closer.
    </string>

    <string name="heCameAloneBBS">
        “You came here alone?” I ask.
        \n“Jackson came with me to show me the way, but then he went home,” he replies.
        \n“Which Jackson? Jackson Baker?”
        \n“Yeah him.”
        \nI remember Jackson. We went to middle school together… It\'s been a while though.
        \n“Shame… I would have wanted to talk to him too. We used to know each other back in middle school.”
        \n“Really?”
        \n“Yeah. Star Trek Club. We were complete nerds… But at least life was better then.”
        \n“That\'s… Interesting…”
        \n“So uh… I called you here so then I could apologize. Like, I\'ve been… I\'ve been bullying you. And to be honest, it\'s not my fault. Actually, it\'s technically all my fault. But I\'ve been having family problems and all that jazz. I got angry and stuff, but like… I guess I channeled my anger into you instead. I\'m really sorry about that, and if there\'s anything I can do to make up to you… I\'ll do it.”
    </string>

    <string name="heForgaveMeBBS">
        “Well there is one thing…” he starts.
        \n“What is it?” I ask.
        \n“Be my friend. We can start from there instead.”
        \nI really don\'t know what to think. I\'ve been awful to him… I\'ve been a capital jerk.
        \n“You sure about that..?” I ask.
        \n“Yeah. Instead of making bad memories, we can replace them with good ones. And I feel like you\'re being sincere and all that… So… If you don\'t mind, maybe we can be friends!”
        \n“I… Yeah, let\'s be friends. I\'m still sorry that I-”
        \n“Drop it. Let it go. I don\'t care. The past is gone, okay? We should start from the beginning.”
        \nHe stick out my hand.
        \n“Hi, my name is Justin Banks. What\'s your name?”
        \n“I\'m Roman Thanos,” I smile, taking his hand in a firm grasp.
        \n“Pleased to meet you,” he smiles, “So… What do you like to do?”
    </string>

    <string name="heDidntForgiveMeBBS">
        He mutters something I can\'t hear.
        \n“Sorry, what?” I frown.
        \n“There\'s nothing you can do to make up for the damage you\'ve done. I appreciate you defending me against that other guy, but… I don\'t think I can trust you yet. For all I care, you could be luring me into a trap.”
        \n“I\'d never do that.”
        \n“But you have the capability. So… I\'m sorry, but I can\'t forgive you yet.”
        \n“It\'s alright. I guess I just won\'t bother you again...”
        \nI get up and leave. There\'s nothing more I can do. I feel helpless… But the very least I can do is keep my word and never bother him again.
    </string>

    <string name="heCameWithAFriendBBS">
        They arrive at the park. The boy waves at me. I gives him a small smile.
        \n“Hey,” I says, raising my hand.
        \n“Hi,” he replies.
        \n“Jackson?!” I exclaim, recognizing the other boy.
        \n“Yeah. This is Jackson,” confirms the boy.
        \n“Hey Rome,” says Jackson, saluting me with the Vulcan salute.
        \n“Jackie,” I nod, returning the salute.
        \n“You guys know each other..?!” exclaims the boy, bewildered.
        \n“Middle school,” I explain.
        \n“Yeah… We were in the same club. Some Star Trek thing,” smiles Jackson, “You wouldn\'t know. But high school kind of changed everything. Like, we barely speak with each other. Or see each other, for that fact,” he sighs, then he turns to Roman and says, “Justin asked me to come with him to the park. So I wondered, why did you ask Justin to come?”
        \n“I just wanted someone to talk to,” I explain, “Life\'s been rough. And I\'m not proud to say it, but I\'ve been mean to him. Not just once. I kind of… I kind of channeled my anger into him. I\'m pretty sure he\'s terrified of me. So I thought that maybe he could bring a friend. Someone he could trust. I\'m kind of glad it\'s you.”
        \n“I see... I\'m glad that you\'ve made up with him. He told me about that already, but I needed to hear it from you.”
        \n“You don\'t trust me?!” asks Justin, shocked.
        \n“Of course not,” laughs Jackson.
        \n“Are you scared of me?” I ask.
        \n“Not really,” reply Justin, “Your family situation is kind of terrible.”
        \n“It\'s hell,” I reply, “But I\'m actually pretty happy that I\'m not terrifying. I\'m sorry about everything, and I know I can\'t make everything up to you, but… I don\'t know. So… Do you want to be friends?”
    </string>

    <string name="heSaidYesBBS">
        “Yes. Let\'s be friends,” replies Justin, sticking out his hand.
        \nI shake it. I\'m relieved.
        \n“Great. I\'m glad we can be friends,” I smile.
        \n“Can I join in on the friendship?” jokes Jackson.
        \n“Only if you have those legendary cookies,” I grin.
        \n“You still remember my cookies…” smiles Jackson, “Of course I have them. I was going to give them to Violet, but she\'s apparently allergic to one of the ingredients.”
        \nHe pulls out a bag of cookies from his bag, and hands them to me. I take one and pass the bag to Justin.
        \n“Take one,” I say, “They\'re really good.”
        \n“Thanks,” he replies, taking a cookie.
        \n“Three cheers for friendship!” shouts Jackson.
        \n“That\'s really tacky,” replies Justin, my voice muffled by a cookie.
        \n“HIP HIP, HURRAY!” shout Jackson and I.
        \n“I can\'t believe you did that,” laughs Justin.
        \n“I\'d do anything for a friend,” I smile.
        \nI bite into the cookie. It\'s delicious, just the way I remember it. It really brings out old memories… But the past is passed, and now is the day to turn over a new leaf.
    </string>

    <string name="heSaidNoBBS">
        “No. I can\'t. I\'m sorry,” he replies.
        \nIt\'s not his fault. It\'s mine. I\'ve been too aggressive towards him. There\'s no way I can make it up to him.
        \n“I understand…” I sigh, “Well, it was worth asking anyway.”
        \nJackson pulls Justin aside. They whisper a bit.
    </string>

    <string name="justinReturnsBBS">
        Justin turns back to me.
        \n“You know what?” he starts, “I changed my mind. Let\'s be friends.”
        \nI smile. I can\'t believe he wants to be my friend...
        \n“Thanks Justin. I hope we\'ll get along…” I grin.
        \n“And also, I accept your apology,” he says.
        \n“Thank you,” I reply, tearing up.
        \n“Oh god. Please don\'t cry.”
        \nI really shouldn\'t cry. I think of the best excuse I can think of.
        \n“I was yawning,” I say quickly.
        \n“Oh…”
    </string>

    <string name="justinLeavesBBS">
        Justin turns back to face me.
        \n“Sorry about that, but I just realized that I need to go home.”
        \n“It\'s okay,” I replies.
        \nI\'m sad. Jackson also looks a bit disappointed. He turns around and starts walking away. It doesn\'t matter anyway. Nothing matters any more. I guess I just won\'t bother him again.
        \n“Hey man, you okay?” I ask Jackson.
        \n“Yeah… He just told me that we aren\'t friends anymore.”
        \n“That\'s harsh.”
        \n“Sorry, I meant that he told me that we weren\'t friends to begin with.”
        \n“That sucks.”
        \n“I think your situation seems worse. Why did you bother him in the first place, anyway?”
        \n“I… I had some family problems. I took my anger out on him.”
        \n“You used to be different, you know. A lot more likeable.”
        \n“I\'m sorry!” I snap, “If my mom didn\'t decide to… To go out and meet new people, maybe I wouldn\'t be like this! I hate her lifestyle right now, and I hate the guys she\'s with.”
        \n“Rome. Calm. Down.”
        \n“I\'m sorry,” I say, and I start swinging on my swing.
        \n“Hey,” says Jackson quietly, “If you ever need someone to talk to, I\'ll be here for you alright?”
        \nI look at him incredulously. I guess… I guess I do trust him.
        \n“Alright. Thank you so much...”
        \n“I have been, and always shall be, your friend,” he quotes.
    </string>
</resources>