<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name ="BeginningGVS">
        First period. I hate first period. Why? Because Ashley is there.
        She\'s also there in two other of my four classes, but first period is the worst.
        \nWho\'s Ashley? She\'s the queen bee, and she hates me with a passion.
        You\'d imagine that first period would be laid back but NOPE, not for me.
        I get to undergo the torturous looks of the Queen Bee herself.
        I sit beside her and her minions, and they make me feel self conscious.
        During first period, she loves ganging up on me with her minions, humiliating me in front of the class.
        They call me names, have other students in the class ignore me, pull out nasty tricks and cruel jokes.
        And that\'s just the tip of the iceberg!
        \nI let out a sigh and rest my head on the desk, already starting to feel exhausted even though it\'s just the beginning of the day.
        That\'s when I hear some snickers right beside me.
        I turn to the direction of the sound and see one of the Queen Bee\'s minions whispering
        something and pointing her finger at me.
        I have a bad feeling about this.
    </string>

    <string name ="askProblemVGS">
        I muster up my courage stutter, “W-What\'s your problem...”
        \nThe girls all turn around to look at me.
        \n“Never mind,” I whisper, and I turn back to my desk.
        \nThey giggle.
    </string>

    <string name ="stareAtThemVGS">
        I silently stare at them until Ashley notices and gives me a condescending look.
        \n“What do you want, creep. Stop staring at us. Geez,” she says.
        \nShe crumbles a paper and throws it at me, hitting my face. I open the crumbled paper revealing a bunch of disses
        and swearing and an awful drawing of me. Ouch.
    </string>

    <string name ="ignoreThemVGS">
        I turn back, facing at my desk. Nothing good will come out of interacting with them.
        I should just ignore them and hope for the class to end soon.
       </string>

    <string name ="classEndsVGS">
        Class ends quickly and I pack up my things, feeling the eyes of Ashley and her “buddies”.
        I pull my bag up onto my shoulder only being stopped to do so. I turn around and see Ashley\'s friend Jade opening my bag.
    </string>

    <string name ="stareVGS">
        I quickly lock eyes with her.
        \n“Hey brat. You have anything to give me?” she asks as she tugs onto my bag.
        I turn to the teacher only to notice that he\'s gone and the next class is coming in.
        \n“You don\'t want to create a scene do you?”
    </string>

    <string name ="askWhatSheWantVGS">
        “Y-y-yes?”
        \n“Hey Violet. Think you can send me the homework answers?”
        \n“U-uh…”
        \n“Don\'t worry, I\'ll return it later.”
        \nI\'m quite certain that she won\'t.
    </string>

    <string name="beAggresiveVGS">
        “L-let go of my bag! Leave me alone!”
        \nI desperately tug my bag away from her.
        \n“Woah, woah. Hold it there, brat.”
        \nShe tightens her grasp on my bag.
        \n“Just be obedient and quietly hand over your things unless you wanna get beat up.”
    </string>

    <string name ="tugOnBagHardVGS">
        “Stop struggling!”
        \nJade becomes even forceful, yanking my bag.
        \n*rip*
        \nMy bag rips (almost) in half, causing all of my stuff to pour out. Thankfully, it\'s still somewhat intact.
        \n“Tch. You shoulda just been obedient," says Jade as she pushes me onto the floor.
        \nShe takes some of my belongings and leaves the classroom.
        I let out a sigh and stuff my belongings back into the worn-out-three-months-old-bag.
    </string>

    <string name ="giveUpBagVGS">
        “Good,” says Jade, taking something out of my bag and leaves.
        \nAt least she didn\'t do anything else.
        I silently mourn the loss of my belongings while heading over to my next class.
    </string>

    <string name ="helpVGS">
        I catch everyone\'s attention by screaming my head off. Jade\'s eyes widen as everyone focuses on us.
        \n“Violet, stop screaming! We\'re in school, you idiot!” she exclaims, smacking my head.
        \nI immediately stop screaming, stunned by the blow. Everyone is mumbling. Some people are laughing.
        Others are pointing at me. Jade looks smug. She grabs my backpack, pulls something out, then drops my bag beside me and leaves…
        What did she take...
    </string>

    <string name = "secondPeriodVGS">
        The bell rings for second period. We start to take out tools to conduct a chemistry experiments for science class.
        I groan as I take out the materials. Science class is the class where I make the most slip-ups.
        Of course, it\'s not because of me, but because of Ashley.
        She always intervenes and messes up every single one of my experiments, resulting in lectures from my teacher about these
        mishaps of mine.
        There\'s a high chance that Ashley will conduct another assault on me.
    </string>

    <string name= "workAloneVGS">
        I move to a corner and begin setting out all of the equipment I need on the table. Suddenly I am pushed to the ground by someone. Ashley.
        \n“Watch where you\'re going, incompetent.”
        \nShe glares down at me then walks off. I try to ignore what had happened as I get back onto my feet and resume what I was doing.
        As time slowly passes, I keep on working, following the instructions step by step and mixing the chemicals.
        Everything is proceeding well until a wheeze of grey smoke burst out of the test tube I am holding.
        \nI let out a huge “What!?” as more smoke emerges out of the tube.
        The science teacher comes running to my side and screeches at me.
        \n“Violet! What have you done this time!?”
        \n“I-I don\'t know. I was just following the procedures and then it just-”
        \n“Hmm?”
        \nThe teacher inspects at the chemicals I used and then point at one of them.
        \n“Then explain to me why you used the wrong chemicals! Haven\'t I told you to not mistaken this fluid with the other one because it creates dangerous chemical reactions!”
        \n“What?”
        \nI look carefully at the fluid and realize it is a very similar looking fluid, but the wrong one.
        \n“But I remember checking that I had the right-”
        \nIt was then I realized that the fluids were switched, when I was pushed by Ashley. I look at the gang. They\'re quietly snickering at me.
        \n“Teacher, i-it wasn\'t me-”
        \n“No excuses! For not listening to my instructions and creating a mess, you\'re getting a detention!”
        \nI slump down as I get assigned for an upcoming detention. No words can get through the teacher\'s head now that she\'s like that. Not only that, the rest of the school time was pretty much disastrous.
    </string>

    <string name="joinGroup">
        I walk up to two girls and ask, “Um, can I watch you guys conduct the experiment? I don\'t really get it.”
        \n“Sure,” the two girls nod, “why not.”
        \nI thank them and sighed in relief. I don\'t think Ashley will come bother me now that I\'m mingled with other people like this…..for now.
        After a short while, one of the girls broke the silence and asked,
        \n“Hey, have you heard about some rumors concerning Ashley?"
    </string>

    <string name="whatAbout">
        \n“It seems that she\'s having some family issues,” the girl answers.
        \n“Her?”
        \n“Yep, I\'ve heard about it from her minio-I mean, friends. She\'s in quite the depression.”
        \n“Hmm...”
        \nSo even the queen bee can have issues...If the rumor\'s true, that is.
    </string>

    <string name="noIDontCare">
        “Okay,” says the girl as she changes the conversation to another topic.
        I don\'t really want to or bother to know more about Ashley. Nothing good comes up when it\'s about her anyway.

        \nTime peacefully passes and the period ends without a hitch. Well that\'s a relief

    </string>

    <string name ="endOfSchool">
        FINALLY, school ended. It was a really long day and I still have to repeat this four more times until the weekend, where I get a break.
        And then torture starts again after that. It was a never-ending long cycle. I cringed at the thought of that. I then try to cheer myself up as I walk towards the exit.
        \n“It\'s okay. Nothing\'s alright, but I can still keep on going.”
        \nThat\'s right. I still have my friend, and that person to support me.
        \nIt was just then, when I happen to witness a girl and a boy walking together through the hallway. It took me a few seconds for it to circulate through my head.
        It wasn\'t just anyone, but was Ashley, and Jackson.
        \nJackson Baker was someone who saved me out of my despair and loneliness.
        He would talk to me like an equal, listen to any of my anxieties and treat me kindly despite my awkwardness.
        Thanks to him, I was able to act more normally and fit in school. But things changed after the weekend.
        \nHe no longer started talk to me.
        He kept hanging out with Ashley and no longer asked me if anything was wrong, just like what he used to do before the weekend.
        \n\'Things change I guess\' and I started walking home by myself.
    </string>

    <string name = "nextDayVGS">
        I usually wake up to the sound of my alarm clock ringing, but today wasn\'t the reason.
        School starts at 8… And it\'s way past that time.
        \n“SHOOT IM LATE” and i run towards the washroom and quickly get ready.
        \n“Hey sweetie, no lover wake-up call today?” I hear my mother say jokingly.
        \n“Yeah yeah whatever mom,” I reply tearfully while quickly munching on a nutrient bar.
        \n“Hey sweetie, what\'s wrong?” asks my dad.
        \n“It-It\'s nothing” I say, “I gotta go..”
        \nI shove the rest of the nutrient bar into my mouth and take a step outside allowing me to have my own reflecting time.
        \nToday I went through a short-cut, also known as the park where Jackson and I met. I follow a curving pathway and stopped.
    </string>

    <string name = "kissing">
        There, sitting on the swings kissing/was Ashely and with her wasn\'t her minions, it was Jackson. MY Jackson.
    </string>

    <string name= "getMad">
        My eyes are lying. He wouldn\'t be with her. It\'s impossible. No… Out of everyone.. He has to be with her. All I can see is red.
        I can\'t handle this relationship with Jackson anymore. He was there when I told him I got bullied. He knows my bully is the one with him right now.
        \nRushing towards them with tears running down my face I punch Jackson in the shoulder, cause them to let go of each other.
        \n“I. HATE. YOU” I scream. “We\'re..."
        \nI turn and run to school. The last thing I hear was “WAIT! VI-”
    </string>

    <string name="hideAndEavesdrop">
        No… This can\'t be happening. I quickly take deep breathes cancelling my panic attack.
        \n\'Maybe they aren\'t..together.. Maybe they\'re just talking\' I think to myself.
        \nI remember the secret spot I used to hide near the swings. Maybe I can hear what they\'re saying.
        \nI slowly walk to the hidden area surrounded by shrubs and sit down on the grass and hear Ashely crying. Wait. THE Ashely is crying?!
        \n“Hey, I promise everything is going to be fine”
        \n“I.. don\'t know.. I feel like it wont be. My brother… my family is breaking apart..”
        \n“Hey. It\'s going to be fine”
        \nAnd Ashely turned her head up and looked at Jackson
        \n“Promise?” she says with a pout
        \nAnd Jackson started nodding while patting her on the back.
        \nSo… The rumour was true, Ashely really do have family problems.. But.. What\'s her reason for bullying me..
        \nI dust myself off and turn around while the \'couple\' continue whatever they\'re doing. But why.. Jackson… Why MY Jackson.. Why him..?
    </string>

    <string name = "pretendDontSee">
        Taking deep breaths, I can do this. I should of known. I knew every girl in the school was eyeing Jackson.
        I should of know that the Queen Bee would take dibs on him. I should of known it all along. I can do this.
        \nI trudged down the path like an army man, and leave the park.
    </string>

    <string name ="AtSchool">
        I\'m finally at school. After witnessing that.. I couldn\'t take another hit. It\'s like...
        \nI\'m everyone\'s punching bag… Even the one who I trust the most... But.. where is mine…
        \nSplashing some water on my face I look into the mirror  only to be greeted by a bloodshot eyed girl. I quickly swipe on some eyeliner to make my eyes look less bloodshot
        \n*RINGGG* went the bell.
        \nSighing, I quickly left the washroom and headed to class only to be greeted by my teachers stern face.
        \n“Sorry sir.. I had to do something..” I say while looking at the floor.
        \n“It\'s fine.”
        \nI quickly walk to my seat. I hear snickering as I pass everyone.
        \n“Hey EMO GIRL!” yells Jade.
    </string>

    <string name = "lookAtHer">
        I take a quick look at her and gain eye contact. Beside her is Ashley, who looks the same, except she has an entertained look.
        I notice she is looking at my shoe. I quickly look down and see that I have a meter long line of toilet paper trailing behind me…
        I must\'ve stepped on it on the way out… I quickly take it off and shoved it into the side pocket of my bag.
    </string>

    <string name ="yes">
        I quickly muster up the courage and say, “yes?”
        \nI just admitted that I was the \'emo girl\'... I don\'t even dress like an emo!
        I mean, yeah I dyed my hair but still…
        \n“Look at your foot.”
        \nI look down and feel my face starts to burn up.
        Of course such a cliche thing happens to me. I have a meter long line of toilet paper stuck on my shoe.
    </string>

    <string name ="nurseChat">
        Sitting myself down, I take a deep breath. That was stressful. The teacher continued to blab.
        \nI hope I don\'t deal with Ashley anymore today.. Least this period..  I felt my eyes close on themeslves. Wait.
        \nDon\'t tell me I\'m falling asleep now. What.. and I fainted.
        \n\nI woke up in the infimiry and was greeted by the nurse.
        \n“I see that you\'ve woken up now. How are you feeling?”
        \nI hear as I sit up on the makeshift bed only to be given a cup of warm water.
        \n“Thank you.” I say as I take a sip. “You fainted due to stress. What\'s wrong sweetie?”
        \nI hear as I turn to face the nurse. “I feel like no one wants me anymore” I say with a sigh and gave back the empty cup.
        \n“At least 1 person will want you. Everyone is unique in their own little way.
        \nSometimes you have to talk to the others to understand why they don\'t like you and understand what is going on in their shoes. “
        \nI replied with a nod and stood up, while saying, “I\'m feeling a lot better now.”
        \n“If you want you can go home, you are already on sick leave for your last period.
        \nWe can call your parents to come and pick you up” I hear her say with a smile.
        \n“Okay,  think that will be better” I reply with a smile and called my parents.
    </string>

    <string name = "atHome">
        The nurses\' words were ringing in my head: take a step into the other\'s shoes. What was bothering Ashely? What happened.
        Were the rumours true? Was she really in the depression? The only way for me to find out is to ask… But am I capable to do so?
        \n“You okay sweetheart?” I hear my mom say as she closed the door behind me.
        \n“It\'s nothing mom…” I say while heading up to my room.
    </string>

    <string name = "inMyRoom">
        Peace and quiet. No one to bother me. No one to bully me. Just me myself and I. Flopping onto my bed I close my eyes and fall into a deep slumber.
    </string>

    <string name ="theNextDay">
        I can do this. Take a step into the other\'s shoes and see what they\'re going through. I can do this, I take multiple deep breaths and walk down the stairs.
        \nKnowing that Ashely will be with Jackson wil be easy for me to find her. I takeout my phone and send Jackson a message.
        \n"Hey. Can you help me with something?”
        \n“Whats up?”
        \n“I need to meet up with Ashely so I can talk to her, can you tell her to meet me under the bleachers after school today?”
        \n“Okay. and hey, I don\'t see you around anymore, whats wrong sweetheart?”
        \nReading the last final message I quickly shove my phone into my pocket. I mean, he\'s always with Ashley nowadays of course he will forget about me.. Right?
        \nTaking a step into the school, I hurry up into the halls and disappear into the crowd.
    </string>

    <string name ="meetingAshely">
        It\'s time to meet the Queen Bee. I can do it.
        I just have to talk to her about what is wrong and how she treating me badly can lead to difficult situations, not only for me but also for her.
        \nWalking down the bleachers I watch the soccer team practice, and with a sharp turn, I am under the bleachers with a sassy looking Ashley.
        \n“So what can i do for you Violet?” I hear her say and reply with. “What did i do to you Ashley? I never harmed you, what made you treat me the way I\'m being treated?”
        \n“Its… nothing really..” and she started to tear up. What was wrong with her, was it something major?
        \n“Hey Ashley, you can tell me anything I promise I won\'t tell a soul.” I say and I quickly sat down beside her.
    </string>

    <string name = "goodEnd">
        “You know,” she starts, “I\'m really sorry for picking on you. It\'s not that I don\'t like you or anything, it\'s just that I… I needed someone to lash out on. I feel like something inside me just like, snapped when my parents said that they were going to get divorced. Like… I don\'t know. I cried so much. And the thing with Jackson… He gave me a shoulder to cry on when I was at my lowest. Ther\'s nothing going on between us. Trust me, he\'s a good guy. Don\'t dump him.  But I\'m really sorry if I made it look like we we\'re together or something like that.”
        \n“Thanks Ashley,” I reply.
        \n“You know,” says Ashley, “You\'d look hotter if you tried using eyeliner. Not saying that you\'re not hot already. Wanna go shopping some time?”
        \n“Sure.”
        \n“Here, give me your number,” she replies, handing me her phone.
        \nI give her my number, and we part ways. Now that I know what really happened, I think Jackson and I… It might work out. I walk to his house (it\'s a quick ten minute walk anyway) and press the doorbell. He answers the door.
        \n“Oh… Hey Violet. What\'s up?”
        \n“Look, Jackson… I just want you to know that I still love you, and I want you to forgive me. I know you\'re probably angry, and I know you probably don\'t really want to talk with me, but the thing with Ashley, I just⎼”
        \nHe steps out of his house and hugs me.
        \n“Don\'t worry honey, I wasn\'t angry at you. I missed you so much. I love you too, never forget that. And now that you\'re here,” he continues, taking my hands in his, “I know this isn\'t very romantic, but I need to ask you now... Will you go to prom with me?”
        \n“Yes!”
    </string>

</resources>