<resources>
    <string name ="b_g">
        “No. Stop crying. You\'re fine,” I tell to myself while staring at my reflection.
        \nQuickly wiping my face, I hear a knock on the door.
        \n“Sweetheart, are you okay?” asks my mom.
        \n“Yeah mom. I\'m fine," I say, while opening the door and pushing her away.
        \n“I know this is a lot to take in sweetie… This divorce means so much to us... but just know we\'re doing this for the famil-”
        \n“MOM JUST SHUT UP! YOU KNOW HOW MUCH MY BROTHER MEANS TO ME!”
        \nI slam the front door and hop onto my shiny black Lincoln Mark VIII, a present my brother gave me once I got my G2.
        \nSlamming on the accelerator, I pull out of the driveway and head towards the only place that could make me happy.
    </string>

    <string name ="theParkGBS">
        Ah... The park. I stare at the children in the sand and swinging on the swings.
        \nI wish I was that small… Not needing to worry about …
        I look down, knowing that the tears are about to come again.
        \n“Hey, you alright there?”
        \nI look up only to see an angel sent from the heavens.
        \n“Um. yeah. Why would I not be fine?” I snap, only to see his beautiful green eyes widen.
        \n“I mean... You were just there crying…” he says.
        \n“Sorry. I… I\'m just having a bad day” I reply.
        \n“Well do you want to talk about it?” he asks, and he sits beside me.
        \nWe continue the conversation for an hour or two only to end up asking each other where we go to school.
        \n“Woah same.”
        \n“Cool. I hope we see each other in the hall,” I say quickly and run back to my car only to turn around and see him gone.
    </string>

    <string name="theSchoolGBS">
        Great idea, me. I\'ll just go to school... It\'s the best place to go to when you\'re feeling sad! JUST KIDDING!
        \nI drive to the nearest place I could think of - my Aunt\'s place.
        \n“Oh hey there, pumpkin, what brings you here?” says my Aunt while I slam my car door close.
        \n“Hey Aunt Janet, mind if I stay here for a little bit?”
        \n“Whatever you say sweetheart, it\'s up to you… Did your mother tell you the news?"
        \n“No. Don\'t tell me you knew it too.” I stutter while opening their front door.
        \nI turn around and go home.
    </string>

    <string name ="nextDayBGS">
        I take a step out of my room only to remember the argument and that my parents are going to get divorced, causing my brother and I to split up.
        \nI quickly enter the washroom and finish up looking and smelling good. With a flick of mascara, I exit the washroom and hurry into my closet. Laid out on my bed was the outfit I picked the night before. Putting it on, I run down the stairs and ignore my parents asking me what I want for breakfast. I run into my car and think to myself: There\'s still an hour before school starts, what am I gonna do. I most definitely won\'t get to school... What about the park?
        \nI step on the accelerator and off I go.
    </string>

    <string name ="atTheParkBGS">
        I arrive and take a seat on the swings. It\'s so peaceful. No crazy screaming kids, none of that sort. Suddenly I hear someone approaching, and I turn to see Jackson Baker, the nice boy who\'s always with that emo girl, whatever her name is.
        \n“Hey, Ashely right?”
        \nI look up and meet up with his green eyes. There\'s something about his eyes that make me feel so normal around him... His personality reminds me of my brother.
        \n“Um… Hi. Yes. I\'m Ashley,” I stammer.
        \n“You probably don\'t know who I am, but the name is Jackson Baker.”
        \n“I know who you are. I mean... Yeah, day one intro,” I reply, trying to keep my cool.
        \n“Well, that\'s great! So what\'s with the down face?” he asks with concern.
        \n“It\'s nothing,” I reply, covering up with a small flip of my hair.
        \n“You sure? I mean, I see you storm out of your house pretty much every day...”
        \nI raise a finely tuned eyebrow at him. Creepy stalker.
        \n“I mean.. I\'m your neighbour,” he explains, “I\'m not trying to seem creepy or anything, but we live pretty close, and I like to work with my blinds up.”
        \n“Maybe I\'ll tell you the next time I see you,” I reply.
        \nThen my phone rings. I pick it up.
        \n“Hello?” I say.
        \n“Hey girl, where you at?”
        \nIt\'s Jade.
        \n“Just wandering around, as usual.”
        \n“You have your car right? Can you drive me to school? I got some deats,” she giggles.
    </string>

    <string name ="sureBGS">
        “Yeah sure, now?”
        \n“Woah. I thought you would say no.”
        \n“I mean these have to be important if you want me to drive you,” I smirk
        \n“Yeah, it totally is.”
        \nI hang up on her.
        \n“Sorry Jackson, I gotta go,” I tell him.
        \n“No problem, I\'ll see you around.”
        \nI run to my car and drive away.
    </string>

    <string name ="noBGS">
        “How about you tell me during our lunch,” I smirk.
        \n“But I might forget about it.”
        \n“Well then text it to me!”
        \n“But I wanna-”
        \n“No buts.”
        \nI hang up. Getting information from Jade can be exhausting sometimes.
    </string>

    <string name = "yeahButNextTimeIWontBGS">
        “Um. yeah sure, I guess since there\'s nothing to do. But next time I\'m not doing anything for you. You have your own car,” I snap.
        \nI end the call and check the time. I noticed we only had 15 minutes left.
        \n“Gotta run, I\'ll talk to you at school. Just call me,” I tell Jackson as I get into my car.
        \n“Wait I don\'t-”
        \nI slam my door and drive off.
    </string>

    <string name = "atSchoolBGS">
        I take a deep breath. I. CAN. DO. THIS. Flashing my shining smile in the front mirror I leave my car. Suddenly a bunch of people rush towards me, asking me if I had heard about the news.
        \n“Nah. I don\'t the deats. Whats up?” I say.
        \n“You know Violet?”
        \n“Uh no?”
        \n“Well she\'s the emo girl and she\'s been hooking up with Jackson.”
        \n“Wait. The emo girl and Jackson Bakers?” I reply, shocked.
        \n“Yeah!”
        \nThen the bell rang and everyone disappeared to their classes.
        \n“So.. I guess you heard the news right?” asks a voice.
        \nI turn my head only to see Jade.
        \n“Yeah, emo girl and Jackson are dating or something.”
        \n“Jackson Baker, not just any other nerdy guy but THE Jackson Baker”
        \n“Yeah, I guess it sucks to be the emo girl” I smirk.
        \n“I thought you liked him or something,” she smiles.
        \n“Ew. No. Me and him? Never.”
        \n“Okay then,” she grins.
        \nWe go to class.
    </string>

    <string name ="duringClassBGS">
        I take a step into the class and flash my brilliant smile. I strut down the side of the class and sit gracefully at my desk. Jade sits beside me. Violet sits in front of us, but we normally don\'t pay much attention to her.
        \n“Hey it\'s Violet,” whispers Jade, pointing at Violet, “Let\'s do something.”
        \n“Sure,” I smirk,
        \nIn front of us, Violet turned and stared at us with a confused face. She probably heard her name.
    </string>

    <string name = "afterClassBGS">
        “What was that about” asks Stella, one of my friends.
        \n“Dunno,” snickers Jade.
        \nWe watch Violet struggle to put her huge bag onto her back. What a struggle.
        \n“I have an idea,” grins Jade.
        \nShe goes up to Violet and opens her bag. She then grabs her pencil case and her notes. We take off laughing into second period, holding the things that we snatched from her bag.
    </string>

    <string name ="secondPeriodBGS">
        Going into the science lab was one of the best moments of my day. I can do so much to Violet. But.. Why do i treat her like this...
        \nShe\'s done nothing to me. Just thinking about this reminds me of my family… Why must my parents do this to me... We were a happy family yesterday!
        \nSpeaking of Violet, I look up and see her entering the class, looking terrified. I grin. Forget about my issues. What can go wrong with a bunch of unknown substances and compounds?
        \nThe teacher starts talking, causing us to all be quiet. So we\'re doing a group science lab experiment. I look at Jade and she smiles. Partners!
        \n“Hey, Ash, wanna do something with Violet?” asks Jade as she sits beside me.
        \nViolet\'s alone by the table next to us.
        \n“Sure,” I smile.
        \nI push Violet over, and she falls on the table top, Jade swaps her chemicals around.
        \n“Sorry Violet, didn\'t see you there,” I smile.
        \nI turn back to Jade, and we exchange smiles. We continue on with our chem lab when suddenly...
        \n“BOOM”
        \nWe immediately knew who it is. We turn our heads towards Violet and we see her covered in a grey dust. We watch the science teacher go running towards Violet.
        \n“Violet!” he yells, “What have you done this time!?”
        \n“I-I don\'t know,” she stammers, “I was just following the procedures and then it just…”
        \n“Hmm...”
        \nThe teacher inspects the chemicals Violet used and then points to one of them yelling, “Then explain to me why you used the wrong chemicals! Haven\'t I told you to not mistaken this fluid with the other one because it creates dangerous chemical reactions!”
        \n“What?!” says a very confused Violet.
        \n“Well yeah, cause we switched them duh,” mutters Jade under her breath.
        \nI suppress a smile.
        \nViolet looks very carefully at the fluids and stutters, “But I remember checking that I had the right-”
        \n“No excuses! For not listening to my instructions and creating a mess, you\'re getting a detention!” snaps the teacher.
        \nWe snicker. Violet looks at our teacher. We continue our lab project, smirking the entire time.
        \nWe smile to ourselves, knowing that we got Violet into detention with a very strict teacher.
    </string>

    <string name ="endOfSchoolBGS">
        Finally, school ended. I don\'t need to worry about how others think about me at school. Grabbing my things from my locker, I turn around only to get scared by Jackson.
        \n“Oh my gosh, you scared me,” I smile.
        \n“Sorry Ashley, didn\'t mean to scare you.”
        \n“It\'s good,” I reply, quickly closing my locker and struggling to sling my bag over my shoulder.
        \n“I know I shouldn\'t be doing this but if you wanna vent, I\'ll be at the park every morning. Do you want me to carry something? Your bag looks heavy,” he says.
        \n“Sure,” I reply.
        \nHe quickly pulls it up on his shoulder. We start walking down the hallway we head out to my car.
        \n“Hey… Can I have a ride? We do live close to each other...” he asks, putting my bag into the trunk.
        \nI stare at him, not knowing if he\'s being cute or creepy. I reply with:
    </string>

    <string name = "sureJacksonBGS">
        \n“Sure, get in,” I say, getting into my car.
    </string>

    <string name ="whyJacksonBGS">
        “Uh, why?” I ask him hesitantly.
        \n“I mean it\'s just a carpool right? And well i don\'t want to walk home” he replies while walking to the passenger side.
        \nHopefully, this won\'t harm my reputation. I nod, and we drive.
    </string>

    <string name ="noJacksonBGS">
        “Sorry, I just want to go home” I say and he nods.
        \n“I understand. After all you\'ve been through, you definitely need some time alone.”
        \nI feel my tears coming back up into my eyes.
        \n“Maybe next time,” I smile.
        \nI enter my car and start driving away.
    </string>

    <string name= "theNextDayBGS">
        I wake up early to do my usual schedule. I decide to go talk to my brother. He\'s still sleeping.
        \n“Hey bro... It sucks so much that the family is going to split up...”
        \n“Let me sleep,” he croaks, burying his head underneath his pillow.
        \nI leave him alone. I grab a fruit cup and head outside. Maybe i should go to the park again… to see if Jackson is there…
        \nHopping into my car, I start the engine and swiftly turn out of the driveway.
    </string>

    <string name ="atThePark2BGS">
        I arrive at the park, with a fruit cup in hand. I take a seat on one of the benches and start eating my fruit cup. I see someone approaching. That must be Jackson.
        \n“Hey you\'re here,” he says, taking a seat beside me.
        \nI finish my fruit cup.
        \n“Yeah, it\'s calming here,” I reply.
        \n“How are you?” he asks.
        \n“I\'m doing fine for now. This morning was okay, no fighting or yelling.”
        \n“That\'s good,” he replies,  leaning my head on his shoulder.
        \nHe instinctively wraps a protective arm around me.
        \n“You know.. You don\'t have to do this for me..” I say while staring at the sand in the park.
        \n“I i just want what is best for everyone and I promise everything is going to be fine”
        \n“I.. don\'t know.. I feel like it won\'t be. My brother… my family is breaking apart..”
        \nI feel the tears rushing out.
        \n“Hey. It\'s going to be fine,” he says.
        \nI turn to look up at him.
        \n“Promise?” I pout.
        \nHe pats me on the back. Suddenly i hear rustling and look over only to see Violet with tears in her face. Everything went by too fast. I heard Violet screaming and immediately, she turns and runs away with Jackson at her heels. Sighing, I stand and head to my car. Why must my life consist of so much drama?
    </string>

    <string name = "atSchool2BGS">
        Taking a deep breath, I enter the building and head to my locker. I hear everyone say hi, or wave at my and I return a smile to them.
        My reputation is good and all but sometimes it gets annoying to be the constant smile and wave type of person…
    </string>

    <string name = "classBGS">
        I enter the class only to see that Violet was not in class. I hope.. Nothing went wrong between the two… Honestly, they\'re a really cute couple…
        \n5 minutes into class, I hear rapid knocks on the door. I look up and see Violet. The teacher is giving her a stern look. The entire class watches her every move as she walks down the aisle between the desks. A long line of toilet paper was connected to her shoe. I was greatly entertained. Who thought such a cliche thing would occur?
        \nEveryone snickers until Jade yelled out, “Hey EMO GIRL!”
        \nWe all look at her reaction, and I gained eye-contact with Violet and we watched her look down at her foot only to look shocked and shove the meter long toilet paper into her bag and the entire class erupted with laughter. I watch her take a seat and as the teacher spoke about Hamlet, i hear a thud and look into the direction of the sound.
        \nIt was Violet.
    </string>

    <string name= "tellTheTeacherBGS">
        Looking at her pale skin, I quickly stand up, forcing the teacher to look at me.
        \n“Sir. I think Violet fainted. Can i bring her to the infirmary?” I ask.
        \nMy teacher looks surprised. Everyone\'s looking at me. I really hope this is a good idea.
        \n“Of course,” he says.
        \n“Thank you,” I reply, “Can Jade come with me?”
        \n“I\'m not sure that\'s a good idea…”
        \n“She looks really heavy, sir.”
        \nThe teacher looks at Violet, then sighs in resignation.
        \n“Alright then Jade, you can go with Ashley.”
        \nJade and I bring Violet to the infirmary and return to class. Thankfully, no one brings Violet up.
    </string>

    <string name ="ignoreItBGS">
        I quickly turn my head. Class continues. No one really takes notice of her.
        \nAt the end of the class, I look over to Violet. She hasn\'t moved. I watch as her table partner stare at her and look at the teacher. She stands up and I watch her talk to the teacher. Guess I should go home.
    </string>

    <string name ="atHomeBGS">
        I wonder what happened to Violet… Suddenly I hear a crash and thundering footsteps going up the stairs.
        \n“Come on Ashley, we\'re leaving!” I hear my mom shouts.
        \nI look at her in shock.
        \n“But.. mom… Don\'t you still have to sign the..”
        \n“No, we need to go NOW!” she snaps, grabbing my luggage.
        \nWatching her shove all my clothes into it, i started tearing up.
    </string>

    <string name ="inTheCarBGS">
        “Mom, where are we going?” I ask her.
        \n“Aunt Janet\'s house,” she whispers while speeding up.
        \nI look down at my hands and feel my tears fall. I can\'t help it. I don\'t understand…
    </string>

    <string name="nextDay2BGS">
        Last night was hectic. My mother and I went back and forth between my aunt\'s place and my home to get our stuff. At least I have my car now. I quickly change and head out, not even bothering to eat breakfast. I miss my brother... Hopping into my car, I drive to the park.
    </string>

    <string name="atThePark3BGS">
        Running into the park, I see Jackson. He looks up at me. I didn\'t even bother to put on that much makeup today after my cry fest in bed.
        \n“Hey.. you okay?” he asks, looking concerned.
        \nI feel my tears coming back but I keep them in.
        \n“Parents argued, I moved,” I whisper while looking down.
        \n“Hey… Everything is going to be okay,” he says, wrapping me in a hug.
        \nI feel my tears fall down my cheeks. Dang it.
        \n“How do you know,” I whisper.
        \n“Because everything always ends up being okay,” he smiles, releasing me.
        \n“I hope…” I sigh, drying my tears and probably wiping away the remnants of my makeup.
        \n“I got something to ask you. Can you do me a favour?”
        \nTaking a deep breath I look at him and cock my head.
        \n“Sure. Anything.”
        \n“Well, Violet messaged me this morning asking to meet under the bleachers after school today and I was wondering if you could do that for me,” he says
        \nWith a nod I agree. I check the time only to see that I should have gone to school two minutes ago…
    </string>

    <string name ="afterSchool2BGS">
        Time to meet Violet… It\'s for Jackson. Just a small chat, nothing much.
        \n“Hey, Ashe. Wanna go shopping?” Jade asks me.
        \n“Nah I got plans,” I reply, and I head out the classroom to the fields.
        \nI quickly get under the bleachers and sit down on the ground. I hear Violet clunk towards me.
        \n“What can I do for you Violet?” I ask her.
        \n“What did I do to you Ashley? I never harmed you, never did anything to you, really. What made you treat me the way im being treated?” she whispers.
        \n“It\'s...nothing really..” and I start tearing up.
        \nI just wanted an outlet from all the stress my family gave me… I didn\'t mean to be so cruel to her… it just happened…
        \n“Hey Ashley, you can tell me anything... I promise i won\'t tell a soul.”
        \nI hear and she sits down beside me. I bring my legs to my chest and take a deep breathe. Here goes…
    </string>

    <string name ="theEndBGS">
        “You know…” I start, “I\'m really sorry for picking on you. It\'s not that I don\'t like you or anything, it\'s just that I… I needed someone to lash out on. I feel like something inside me just like, snapped when my parents said that they were going to get divorced. Like… I don\'t know. I cried so much. And the thing with Jackson… He gave me a shoulder to cry on when I was at my lowest. There\'s nothing going on between us. Trust me, he\'s a good guy. Don\'t dump him. But I\'m really sorry if I made it look like we were together or something like that. He just reminds me of my brother, that\'s all...”
        \n“I don\'t know what to say…”
        \nWe linger in awkward silence.
        \n“You know, you\'d look hotter if you tried using eyeliner. Not saying that you\'re not hot already. Wanna go shopping some time?” I ask, trying to break the awkwardness.
        \n“Sure… I guess.”
        \nI pull out my phone from my bag and shove it towards her.
        \n“Here, give me your number,” I say.
        \nShe takes my phone and types her number in it. Saying quick goodbyes, I enter my car and smile to myself. I made friends with Violet. Off I go, driving back home with a smile. Everything is going to be a bit better now. Hopefully.
    </string>

</resources>